<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
Maintained 2017-2025 by Gregor Santner <gsantner AT mailbox DOT org>

To the extent possible under law, the person who associated CC0 with
this file has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights
to the public domain.

You should have received a copy of the CC0 legalcode along with this
work. If not, see <https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/>.
-->
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="settings">脨聺脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="light">脨隆脨虏脨碌脩聜脨禄脨掳脩聫</string>
    <string name="dark">脨垄脩聭脨录脨陆脨掳脩聫</string>
    <string name="delete">脨拢脨麓脨掳脨禄脨赂脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="appearance">脨聮脨陆脨碌脩聢脨陆脨赂脨鹿 脨虏脨赂脨麓</string>
    <string name="rename">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨赂脨录脨碌脨陆脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="confirm_delete">脨聼脨戮脨麓脩聜脨虏脨碌脩聙脨麓脨赂脩聜脨碌 脩聝脨麓脨掳脨禄脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="do_you_really_want_to_delete_this_witharg">脨聮脩聥 脨麓脨碌脨鹿脩聛脩聜脨虏脨赂脩聜脨碌脨禄脩聦脨陆脨戮 脩聟脨戮脩聜脨赂脩聜脨碌 脩聝脨麓脨掳脨禄脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聧脩聜脨戮脩聜 %s?</string>
    <string name="confirm_overwrite">脨聼脨戮脨麓脩聜脨虏脨碌脩聙脨麓脨赂脩聜脨碌 脨驴脨碌脩聙脨碌脨路脨掳脨驴脨赂脩聛脩聦</string>
    <string name="file_already_exists_overwerite">脨陇脨掳脨鹿脨禄 脩聝脨露脨碌 脩聛脩聝脩聣脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脩聝脨碌脩聜. 脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨路脨掳脨驴脨赂脩聛脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨碌脨鲁脨戮?</string>
    <string name="browse_filesystem">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨陆脨掳 脩聝脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脩聛脩聜脨虏脨碌</string>
    <string name="title">脨聴脨掳脨鲁脨戮脨禄脨戮脨虏脨戮脨潞</string>
    <string name="empty_directory">脨聼脩聝脩聛脩聜脨掳脩聫 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨掳</string>
    <string name="enter_name_of_folder">脨聮脨虏脨碌脨麓脨赂脩聜脨碌 脨赂脨录脩聫 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="create_folder">脨隆脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脩聝</string>
    <string name="create_new_document">脨隆脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜</string>
    <string name="move">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨录脨碌脩聛脩聜脨赂脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="info">脨聵脨陆脩聞脨戮</string>
    <string name="file_folder_already_exists_please_use_a_different_name">脨陇脨掳脨鹿脨禄 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨掳 脩聝脨露脨碌 脩聛脩聝脩聣脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脩聝脨碌脩聜! 脨聵脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脩聝脨鹿脩聜脨碌 脨麓脩聙脩聝脨鲁脨戮脨碌 脨赂脨录脩聫</string>
    <string name="import_from_device">脨聵脨录脨驴脨戮脩聙脩聜脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聛 脩聝脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脩聛脩聜脨虏脨掳</string>
    <string name="import_">脨聵脨录脨驴脨戮脩聙脩聜脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="append_to_witharg">脨聰脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨潞 %s</string>
    <string name="select_folder">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脩聝</string>
    <string name="edit">脨聽脨碌脨麓脨掳脨潞脩聜脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="search_documents">脨聵脩聛脨潞脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脩聥</string>
    <string name="share_to_arrow" tools:ignore="TypographyEllipsis">脨聼脨戮脨麓脨碌脨禄脨赂脩聜脩聦脩聛脩聫 脩聛芒聙娄</string>
    <string name="share">脨聼脨戮脨麓脨碌脨禄脨赂脩聜脩聦脩聛脩聫</string>
    <string name="search">脨聼脨戮脨赂脩聛脨潞</string>
    <string name="display_converted_markup">脨聽脨碌脨陆脨麓脨碌脩聙脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聙脨掳脨路脨录脨碌脩聜脨潞脩聝</string>
    <string name="editor">脨聽脨碌脨麓脨掳脨潞脩聜脨戮脩聙</string>
    <string name="folders">脨聼脨掳脨驴脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="files">脨陇脨掳脨鹿脨禄脩聥</string>
    <string name="document">脨聰脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜</string>
    <string name="documents">脨聰脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脩聥</string>
    <string name="html_as_plaintext">HTML (脨潞脨掳脨潞 脨驴脩聙脨戮脩聛脩聜脨戮脨鹿 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜)</string>
    <string name="document_editor_font">脨篓脩聙脨赂脩聞脩聜 脨虏 脩聙脨碌脨麓脨掳脨潞脩聜脨戮脩聙脨碌</string>
    <string name="theme">脨垄脨碌脨录脨掳</string>
    <string name="open_existing_files_in_view_mode">脨聻脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聛脩聝脩聣脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脩聝脩聨脩聣脨赂脨碌 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脩聥 脨虏 脩聙脨碌脨露脨赂脨录脨碌 脨驴脩聙脨戮脩聛脨录脨戮脩聜脩聙脨掳</string>
    <string name="about">脨聻 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨赂</string>
    <string name="plaintext">脨聼脩聙脨戮脩聛脩聜脨戮脨鹿 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜</string>
    <string name="file">脨陇脨掳脨鹿脨禄</string>
    <string name="image">脨聵脨路脨戮脨卤脩聙脨掳脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="font_size">脨聽脨掳脨路脨录脨碌脩聙 脩聢脩聙脨赂脩聞脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="render_rtl_language">脨聻脩聜脨戮脨卤脩聙脨掳脨露脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨赂脩聛脩聦脨录脨戮 脩聛脨禄脨碌脨虏脨掳 脨陆脨掳脨驴脩聙脨掳脨虏脨戮</string>
    <string name="error_cannot_create_notebook_dir__appspecific">脨聻脩聢脨赂脨卤脨潞脨掳: 脨陆脨碌 脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聝脩聡脨赂脨禄脨戮脩聛脩聦 脩聛脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脩聝 脨卤脨禄脨戮脨潞脨陆脨戮脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="last_modified_witharg">脨聼脨戮脩聛脨禄脨碌脨麓脨陆脨碌脨碌 脨赂脨路脨录脨碌脨陆脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌: %s</string>
    <string name="last_modified">脨聼脨戮脩聛脨禄. 脩聙脨碌脨麓.</string>
    <string name="select_this_folder">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聝脩聣脩聝脩聨 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脩聝</string>
    <string name="select">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="select_all">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨虏脩聛脨碌</string>
    <string name="create">脨隆脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="select_entries">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聧脨禄脨碌脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脩聥</string>
    <string name="one_item_selected">脨聻脨麓脨赂脨陆 脩聧脨禄脨碌脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜 脨虏脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脨陆</string>
    <string name="items_selected_witharg" tools:ignore="PluralsCandidate">%d 脩聧脨禄脨碌脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脨掳 脨虏脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脨陆脨戮</string>
    <string name="hide_statusbar_at_this_view">脨隆脨潞脩聙脩聥脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脩聝 脩聛脨戮脩聛脩聜脨戮脩聫脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨虏 脩聧脩聜脨戮脨录 脩聙脨碌脨露脨赂脨录脨碌</string>
    <string name="hide_statusbar">脨隆脨潞脩聙脩聥脩聜脩聦 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脩聝 脩聛脨戮脩聛脩聜脨戮脩聫脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="name">脨聵脨录脩聫</string>
    <string name="url_or_path">URL/脨驴脩聝脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="insert_link">脨聮脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聛脩聛脩聥脨禄脨潞脩聝</string>
    <string name="format_link">脨陇脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜 脩聛脩聛脩聥脨禄脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="insert_image">脨聮脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨赂脨路脨戮脨卤脩聙脨掳脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="contributors">脨聽脨掳脨路脩聙脨掳脨卤脨戮脩聜脩聡脨赂脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="save_location">脨隆脨戮脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聙脨掳脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="saved_location_to">脨隆脨戮脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脨碌脨陆脨戮 脨虏 %s</string>
    <string name="select_storage_folder">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脩聝 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="licenses">脨聸脨赂脩聠脨碌脨陆脨路脨赂脨赂</string>
    <string name="changelog">脨聵脩聛脩聜脨戮脩聙脨赂脩聫 脨赂脨路脨录脨碌脨陆脨碌脨陆脨赂脨鹿</string>
    <string name="more_info">脨聰脨戮脨驴脨戮脨禄脨陆脨赂脩聜脨碌脨禄脩聦脨陆脨掳脩聫 脨赂脨陆脩聞脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聠脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="show_license_of_the_app">脨聼脨戮脨潞脨掳脨路脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨禄脨赂脩聠脨碌脨陆脨路脨赂脩聨 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="show_third_party_licenses">脨聼脨戮脨潞脨掳脨路脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聛脩聜脨戮脩聙脨戮脨陆脨陆脨赂脨碌 脨禄脨赂脩聠脨碌脨陆脨路脨赂脨赂</string>
    <string name="language_change_restart_description">脨聵脨路脨录脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聫脨路脩聥脨潞 脩聧脩聜脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫. 脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨路脨掳脨驴脩聝脩聛脩聜脨赂脩聜脨碌 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌, 脩聡脩聜脨戮脨卤脩聥 脨赂脨路脨录脨碌脨陆脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨虏脩聛脩聜脩聝脨驴脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨虏 脩聛脨赂脨禄脩聝</string>
    <string name="language">脨炉脨路脩聥脨潞</string>
    <string name="storage_permission_required">脨聺脩聝脨露脨陆脨戮 脩聙脨掳脨路脩聙脨碌脩聢脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脩聡脩聜脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨赂 脨路脨掳脨驴脨赂脩聛脨赂 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨戮脨虏</string>
    <string name="open_with">脨聻脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脩聜脩聦 脩聛 脨驴脨戮脨录脨戮脩聣脩聦脩聨</string>
    <string name="sort_by">脨隆脨戮脩聙脩聜脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨戮</string>
    <string name="date">脨聰脨掳脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="deleteme____1">脨聵脨录脩聫</string>
    <string name="size">脨聽脨掳脨路脨录脨碌脩聙</string>
    <string name="reverse_order">脨聮 脨戮脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脨陆脨戮脨录 脨驴脨戮脩聙脩聫脨麓脨潞脨碌</string>
    <string name="contribute">脨聮脨陆脨碌脩聛脩聜脨赂 脩聛脨虏脨戮脨鹿 脨虏脨潞脨禄脨掳脨麓</string>
    <string name="project_page">脨隆脩聜脩聙脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聠脨掳 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="press_back_again_to_exit">脨聺脨掳脨露脨录脨赂脩聜脨碌 脗芦脨聺脨掳脨路脨掳脨麓脗禄 脨碌脩聣脩聭 脩聙脨掳脨路, 脩聡脩聜脨戮脨卤脩聥 脨虏脩聥脨鹿脩聜脨赂</string>
    <string name="exit">脨聮脩聥脩聟脨戮脨麓</string>
    <string name="undo">脨聻脩聜脨录脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="redo">脨聮脨碌脩聙脨陆脩聝脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="more">脨聲脩聣脩聭</string>
    <string name="notebook">脨聭脨禄脨戮脨潞脨陆脨戮脩聜</string>
    <string name="help">脨聼脨戮脨录脨戮脩聣脩聦</string>
    <string name="todo_list">脨隆脨驴脨赂脩聛脨戮脨潞 脨麓脨碌脨禄</string>
    <string name="task">脨聴脨掳脨麓脨掳脩聡脨掳</string>
    <string name="context">脨職脨戮脨陆脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜</string>
    <string name="list">脨隆脨驴脨赂脩聛脨戮脨潞</string>
    <string name="priority">脨聮脨掳脨露脨陆脨戮脩聛脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="history">脨聵脩聛脩聜脨戮脩聙脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="sync">脨隆脨赂脨陆脩聟脩聙脨戮脨陆脨赂脨路脨掳脩聠脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="search_or_custom">脨聼脨戮脨赂脩聛脨潞 / 脨聻脩聛脨戮脨卤脩聥脨鹿</string>
    <string name="save">脨隆脨戮脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="update">脨聻脨卤脨陆脨戮脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="clear">脨聻脩聡脨赂脩聛脩聜脨赂脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="due_date">脨隆脩聙脨戮脨潞</string>
    <string name="current_date">脨垄脨碌脨潞脩聝脩聣脨掳脩聫 脨麓脨掳脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="archive">脨聬脩聙脩聟脨赂脨虏脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="add_task">脨聰脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨路脨掳脨麓脨掳脩聡脩聝</string>
    <string name="add_x_witharg">脨聰脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 %s</string>
    <string name="document_to_be_loaded_and_saved_as_witharg">脨聰脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜 脨卤脩聝脨麓脨碌脩聜 脨路脨掳脨鲁脩聙脩聝脨露脨碌脨陆 脨赂 脩聛脨戮脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脩聭脨陆 脨潞脨掳脨潞 \"%s\"</string>
    <string name="refresh">脨聻脨卤脨陆脨戮脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="create_shortcut">脨隆脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聫脩聙脨禄脩聥脨潞</string>
    <string name="tried_to_create_shortcut_for_this_notice">脨隆脨麓脨碌脨禄脨掳脨陆脨掳 脨驴脨戮脨驴脩聥脩聜脨潞脨掳 脩聛脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聫脩聙脨禄脩聥脨潞 脨陆脨掳 脨麓脨戮脨录脨掳脩聢脨陆脨碌脨录 脩聧脨潞脩聙脨掳脨陆脨碌. 脨聺脨碌脨潞脨戮脩聜脨戮脩聙脩聥脨碌 脨麓脨戮脨录脨掳脩聢脨陆脨赂脨碌 脩聧脨潞脩聙脨掳脨陆脩聥 脨陆脨碌 脨驴脨戮脨麓脨麓脨碌脩聙脨露脨赂脨虏脨掳脩聨脩聜 脩聫脩聙脨禄脩聥脨潞脨赂.</string>
    <string name="file_not_in_save_path_do_import_notice__appspecific">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脨陆脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄 脨陆脨掳脩聟脨戮脨麓脨赂脩聜脩聛脩聫 脨陆脨碌 脨虏 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨碌 脨卤脨禄脨戮脨潞脨陆脨戮脩聜脨掳. 脨隆脨潞脨戮脨驴脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨碌脨鲁脨戮 脩聛脩聨脨麓脨掳? 脨聲脩聛脨禄脨赂 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄 脩聛 脩聜脨掳脨潞脨赂脨录 脨赂脨录脨碌脨陆脨碌脨录 脩聛脩聝脩聣脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脩聝脨碌脩聜, 脨戮脨陆 脨卤脩聝脨麓脨碌脩聜 脨驴脨碌脩聙脨碌脨路脨掳脨驴脨赂脩聛脨掳脨陆.</string>
    <string name="file_not_in_current_folder_do_copy__appspecific">脨颅脩聜脨戮脩聜 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄 脨陆脨碌 脨陆脨掳脩聟脨戮脨麓脨赂脩聜脩聛脩聫 脨虏 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聝脩聣脨碌脨鹿 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨碌. 脨隆脨潞脨戮脨驴脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨碌脨鲁脨戮 脩聛脩聨脨麓脨掳? 脨聲脩聛脨禄脨赂 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄 脩聛 脩聜脨掳脨潞脨赂脨录 脨赂脨录脨碌脨陆脨碌脨录 脩聛脩聝脩聣脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脩聝脨碌脩聜, 脨戮脨陆 脨卤脩聝脨麓脨碌脩聜 脨驴脨碌脩聙脨碌脨路脨掳脨驴脨赂脩聛脨掳脨陆.</string>
    <string name="files_and_folders">脨陇脨掳脨鹿脨禄脩聥 脨赂 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="document_browser">脨聻脨卤脨戮脨路脩聙脨碌脨虏脨掳脩聜脨碌脨禄脩聦 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脨戮脨虏</string>
    <string name="file_browser">脨聻脨卤脨戮脨路脩聙脨碌脨虏脨掳脩聜脨碌脨禄脩聦 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨戮脨虏</string>
    <string name="set_due_date">脨拢脩聛脩聜脨掳脨陆脨戮脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聛脩聙脨戮脨潞 脨虏脩聥脨驴脨戮脨禄脨陆脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="insert_replace_date">脨聮脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聝</string>
    <string name="create_note" needed="false">脨隆脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨路脨掳脨录脨碌脩聜脨潞脩聝</string>
    <string name="special_documents" needed="false">脨聻脩聛脨戮脨卤脩聥脨碌 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脩聥</string>
    <string name="keep_screen_on" needed="false">脨聺脨碌 脨戮脩聜脨潞脨禄脩聨脩聡脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聧脨潞脩聙脨掳脨陆</string>
    <string name="disallow_screenshots">脨聴脨掳脨驴脩聙脨碌脩聜脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聛脨潞脩聙脨赂脨陆脩聢脨戮脩聜脩聥</string>
    <string name="back_to_previous_folder" needed="false">脨聮脨碌脩聙脨陆脩聝脩聜脩聦脩聛脩聫 脨虏 脨驴脩聙脨碌脨麓脩聥脨麓脩聝脩聣脩聝脩聨 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脩聝</string>
    <string name="app_settings" needed="false">脨聺脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脨潞脨赂 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="editor_settings" needed="false">脨聺脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脨潞脨赂 脩聙脨碌脨麓脨掳脨潞脩聜脨戮脩聙脨掳</string>
    <string name="remember_last_folder_location_on_startup" needed="false">脨聴脨掳脨驴脨戮脨录脨赂脨陆脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨戮脩聛脨禄脨碌脨麓脨陆脩聨脩聨 脨戮脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脩聜脩聝脩聨 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脩聝</string>
    <string name="number_of_files_witharg" needed="false">脨職脨戮脨禄脨赂脩聡脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脨戮 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨戮脨虏: %d</string>
    <string name="app_wide">脨聻脨卤脩聣脨碌脨碌</string>
    <string name="main_view">脨聯脨禄脨掳脨虏脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脩聧脨潞脩聙脨掳脨陆</string>
    <string name="overall_theme_used_in_app">脨聵脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脩聝脨碌脨录脨掳脩聫 脩聜脨碌脨录脨掳 脨戮脩聞脨戮脩聙脨录脨禄脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="remember_last_directory">脨聴脨掳脨驴脨戮脨录脨赂脨陆脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨戮脩聛脨禄脨碌脨麓脨陆脩聨脩聨 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脩聝</string>
    <string name="syntax_highlighting">脨聼脨戮脨麓脩聛脨虏脨碌脩聜脨潞脨掳 脩聛脨赂脨陆脩聜脨掳脨潞脩聛脨赂脩聛脨掳</string>
    <string name="highlighting_delay">脨聴脨掳脨麓脨碌脩聙脨露脨潞脨掳 脨驴脨戮脨麓脩聛脨虏脨碌脩聜脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="highlighting_delay_lower_value_more_battery_drain_description__appspecific">脨聴脨掳脨麓脨碌脩聙脨露脨潞脨掳 脨虏 脨录脩聛脨碌脨潞 脨驴脩聙脨赂 脨驴脨戮脨麓脩聛脨虏脨碌脩聜脨潞脨碌 脩聛脨赂脨陆脩聜脨掳脨潞脩聛脨赂脩聛脨掳. 脨搂脨碌脨录 脨戮脨陆脨掳 脨录脨碌脨陆脩聦脩聢脨碌, 脩聜脨碌脨录 脨卤脩聥脩聛脩聜脩聙脨碌脨碌 脨戮脨卤脨陆脨戮脨虏脨禄脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌 脨赂 脨卤脨戮脨禄脩聦脩聢脨碌 脩聙脨掳脩聛脩聟脨戮脨麓 脩聧脨陆脨碌脩聙脨鲁脨赂脨赂. 脨隆脩聜脨掳脩聙脩聥脨碌 脩聝脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脩聛脩聜脨虏脨掳 脨录脨戮脨鲁脩聝脩聜 脨路脨掳脨录脨碌脨麓脨禄脩聫脩聜脩聦脩聛脩聫.</string>
    <string name="highlighting_enabled_or_not__appspecific">脨聼脨戮脨麓脩聛脨虏脨碌脩聡脨赂脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨虏脨虏脨碌脨麓脩聭脨陆脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜</string>
    <string name="control_font_size_in_editor">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聙脨掳脨路脨录脨碌脩聙 脩聢脩聙脨赂脩聞脩聜脨掳 脨虏 脩聙脨碌脨麓脨掳脨潞脩聜脨戮脩聙脨碌</string>
    <string name="textactions_show_useful_actions_description__appspecific">脨聼脨戮脨潞脨掳脨路脩聥脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨虏脨陆脨赂脨路脩聝 脨驴脨掳脨陆脨碌脨禄脩聦 脩聛 脨潞脨陆脨戮脨驴脨潞脨掳脨录脨赂. 脨聻脨陆脨赂 脨赂脨路脨录脨碌脨陆脩聫脩聨脩聜 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨路脨掳脨驴脩聝脩聛脨潞脨掳脩聨脩聜 脨麓脨碌脨鹿脩聛脩聜脨虏脨赂脩聫.</string>
    <string name="load_last_opened_folder_at_startup">脨聼脩聙脨赂 脨路脨掳脨驴脩聝脩聛脨潞脨碌 脨路脨掳脨鲁脩聙脩聝脨露脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨戮脩聛脨禄脨碌脨麓脨陆脩聨脩聨 脨戮脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脩聜脩聝脩聨 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脩聝</string>
    <string name="format">脨陇脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜</string>
    <string name="contexts">脨職脨戮脨陆脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜</string>
    <string name="project">脨聼脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜</string>
    <string name="projects">脨聼脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜脩聥</string>
    <string name="none">脨聺脨碌脩聜</string>
    <string name="other">脨聰脩聙脩聝脨鲁脨戮脨碌</string>
    <string name="empty_file">脨聼脩聝脩聛脩聜脨戮脨鹿 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄</string>
    <string name="break_page_pdf_print">脨聺脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聫 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聠脨掳 (PDF/脨驴脨碌脩聡脨掳脩聜脩聦)</string>
    <string name="underline">脨聼脨戮脨麓脩聡脩聭脩聙脨潞脨赂脨虏脨掳脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="underline_hex_color_wether_or_not_to_description__appspecific">脨聼脨戮脨麓脩聡脩聭脩聙脨潞脨赂脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聠脨虏脨碌脩聜脨戮脨虏脩聥脨碌 HEX-脨潞脨戮脨麓脩聥 脨虏 脩聛脨戮脨戮脩聜脨虏脨碌脩聜脩聛脩聜脨虏脨赂脨赂 脩聛 脩聠脨虏脨碌脩聜脨戮脨录</string>
    <string name="underline_hex_color_codes">脨聼脨戮脨麓脩聡脨碌脩聙脨潞脨赂脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聠脨虏脨碌脩聜脨戮脨虏脩聥脨碌 HEX-脨潞脨戮脨麓脩聥</string>
    <string name="insert_current_date_when_starting_new_task">脨聮脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨禄脩聫脩聜脩聦 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聝脩聣脩聝脩聨 脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聝 脨驴脩聙脨赂 脨麓脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨禄脨碌脨陆脨赂脨赂 脨路脨掳脨麓脨掳脩聡脨赂</string>
    <string name="tasks_with_todays_date">脨聴脨掳脨麓脨掳脩聡脨赂 脩聛 脩聛脨碌脨鲁脨戮脨麓脨陆脩聫脩聢脨陆脨碌脨鹿 脨麓脨掳脩聜脨戮脨鹿</string>
    <string name="append_contexts_and_projects">脨聰脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨潞脨戮脨陆脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜 脨赂 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜脩聥</string>
    <string name="append_contexts_and_projects_on_end_of_task">脨聰脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨禄脩聫脩聜脩聦 脨潞脨戮脨陆脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜 脨赂 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜脩聥 脨虏 脨潞脨戮脨陆脩聠脨碌 脨路脨掳脨麓脨掳脩聡脨赂 脨驴脩聙脨赂 脨赂脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脨戮脨虏脨掳脨陆脨赂脨赂 脩聛脨戮脨戮脩聜脨虏脨碌脩聜脩聛脩聜脨虏脩聝脩聨脩聣脨碌脨鲁脨戮 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜脨戮脨虏脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脨麓脨碌脨鹿脩聛脩聜脨虏脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="rtl_rendering">脨聼脨赂脩聛脩聦脨录脨戮 脩聛脨禄脨碌脨虏脨掳 脨陆脨掳脨驴脩聙脨掳脨虏脨戮</string>
    <string name="highlight_line_ending">脨聼脨戮脨麓脩聛脨虏脨碌脩聡脨赂脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨潞脨戮脨陆脨碌脩聠 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="highlight_line_ending_if_two_or_more_spaces">脨聼脨戮脨麓脩聛脨虏脨碌脩聡脨赂脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨卤脨碌脨禄脩聥 脨虏 脨潞脨戮脨陆脩聠脨碌 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞 脩聛 脨麓脨虏脩聝脨录脩聫 脨赂 脨卤脨戮脨禄脨碌脨碌 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨卤脨碌脨禄脨掳脨录脨赂</string>
    <string name="use_monospace_for_code">脨聵脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨录脨戮脨陆脨戮脩聢脨赂脩聙脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脩聢脩聙脨赂脩聞脩聜 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨潞脨戮脨麓脨掳</string>
    <string name="disable_code_block_highlight">脨聻脩聜脨潞脨禄脩聨脩聡脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨戮脨麓脩聛脨虏脨碌脩聜脨潞脩聝 脨卤脨禄脨戮脨潞脨戮脨虏 脨潞脨戮脨麓脨掳</string>
    <string name="auto_renumber_ordered_list">脨聬脨虏脩聜脨戮-脨驴脨碌脩聙脨碌脨陆脩聝脨录脨碌脩聙脨掳脩聠脨赂脩聫 脩聝脨驴脨戮脩聙脩聫脨麓脨戮脩聡脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聥脩聟 脩聛脨驴脨赂脩聛脨潞脨戮脨虏</string>
    <string name="auto_renumber_ordered_list_slowdown">脨聺脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脨潞脨掳 脨录脨戮脨露脨碌脩聜 脨路脨掳脨录脨碌脨麓脨禄脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌.</string>
    <string name="use_different_fonttype_slow_down">脨聵脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聙脨掳脨路脨陆脩聥脨碌 脩聢脩聙脨赂脩聞脩聜脩聥. 脨聰脨赂脨陆脨掳脨录脨赂脩聡脨碌脩聛脨潞脨戮脨碌 脨赂脨路脨录脨碌脨陆脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌 脩聢脩聙脨赂脩聞脩聜脨掳 脨路脨掳脨录脨碌脨麓脨禄脨赂脩聜 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌.</string>
    <string name="general">脨聻脨卤脩聣脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="resources">脨聽脨碌脩聛脩聝脩聙脩聛脩聥</string>
    <string name="space_between_lines_in_percent">脨聹脨碌脨露脨麓脩聝脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脩聡脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨卤脨碌脨禄 脨虏 脨驴脩聙脨戮脩聠脨碌脨陆脩聜脨掳脩聟</string>
    <string name="line_spacing">脨聵脨陆脩聜脨碌脩聙脨禄脨赂脨陆脩聦脩聫脨露</string>
    <string name="archive_does_move_done_tasks">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨录脨碌脩聣脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨虏脩聥脨驴脨戮脨禄脨陆脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聥脨碌 脨路脨掳脨麓脨掳脩聡脨赂 脨虏 脩聝脨潞脨掳脨路脨掳脨陆脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄 脨虏 脩聜脨戮脨鹿 脨露脨碌 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨碌</string>
    <string name="sort_tasks_by_selected_order">脨隆脨戮脩聙脩聜脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨路脨掳脨麓脨掳脩聡脨赂 脨虏 脨虏脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脨陆脨陆脨戮脨录 脨驴脨戮脩聙脩聫脨麓脨潞脨碌</string>
    <string name="special_key">脨隆脨驴脨碌脩聠脨赂脨掳脨禄脩聦脨陆脨掳脩聫 脨潞脨禄脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聢脨掳</string>
    <string name="asciidoc_special_key">脨聺脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脨潞脨赂 AsciiDoc</string>
    <string name="key_page_up">脨聸脨赂脩聛脩聜脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨虏脨虏脨碌脩聙脩聟 (Page Up)</string>
    <string name="key_page_down">脨聸脨赂脩聛脩聜脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨虏脨陆脨赂脨路 (Page Down)</string>
    <string name="key_pos_1">脨聺脨掳脩聡脨掳脨禄脨戮 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脨赂 (Home)</string>
    <string name="key_pos_end">脨職脨戮脨陆脨碌脩聠 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脨赂 (End)</string>
    <string name="key_pos_1_document">脨聺脨掳脩聡脨掳脨禄脨戮 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="key_pos_end_document">脨職脨戮脨陆脨碌脩聠 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="move_text_one_line_up">脨隆脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脩聝 脨虏脨虏脨碌脩聙脩聟</string>
    <string name="move_text_one_line_down">脨隆脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脩聝 脨虏脨陆脨赂脨路</string>
    <string name="start_new_line_below">脨聺脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聫 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脨掳</string>
    <string name="select_current_line">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聧脩聜脩聝 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脩聝</string>
    <string name="key_ctrl_a">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨虏脩聛脩聭 (Ctrl+A)</string>
    <string name="key_tab">脨垄脨掳脨卤脩聝脨禄脩聫脩聠脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="zero_width_space">脨聼脩聙脨戮脨卤脨碌脨禄 脨陆脩聝脨禄脨碌脨虏脨戮脨鹿 脩聢脨赂脩聙脨赂脨陆脩聥</string>
    <string name="em_space">脨聰脨禄脨赂脨陆脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨卤脨碌脨禄 (&amp;emsp;)</string>
    <string name="start_on_bottom">脨聻脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨虏脨陆脨赂脨路脩聝</string>
    <string name="start_on_bottom_when_loading_document">脨聼脨戮脩聛脨禄脨碌 脨路脨掳脨鲁脩聙脩聝脨路脨潞脨赂 脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨潞脩聝脩聙脩聛脨戮脩聙 脨虏 脨潞脨戮脨陆脨碌脩聠 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="unordered_list_character">脨聴脨陆脨掳脨潞 脨陆脨碌脩聝脨驴脨戮脩聙脩聫脨麓脨戮脩聡脨碌脨陆脨陆脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脩聛脨驴脨赂脩聛脨潞脨掳</string>
    <string name="character_to_start_items_of_unordered_list_with">脨聴脨陆脨掳脨潞 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨戮脨卤脨戮脨路脨陆脨掳脩聡脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨陆脨碌脩聝脨驴脨戮脩聙脩聫脨麓脨戮脩聡脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聥脩聟 脩聛脨驴脨赂脩聛脨潞脨戮脨虏</string>
    <string name="unordered_list_char_dash">脨聰脨碌脩聞脨赂脩聛-脨录脨赂脨陆脩聝脩聛 (-)</string>
    <string name="unordered_list_char_asterisk">脨聴脨虏脩聭脨路脨麓脨戮脩聡脨潞脨掳 (*)</string>
    <string name="unordered_list_char_plus">脨聼脨禄脩聨脩聛 (+)</string>
    <string name="filemanager_doesnot_supply_required_data__appspecific">Portal 脨录脨戮脨露脨碌脩聜 脩聙脨碌脨麓脨掳脨潞脩聜脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聜脨戮脨禄脩聦脨潞脨戮 脨禄脨戮脨潞脨掳脨禄脩聦脨陆脩聥脨碌, 脨掳脨虏脩聜脨戮脨陆脨戮脨录脨陆脨戮 脨麓脨戮脩聛脩聜脩聝脨驴脨陆脩聥脨碌 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脩聥 脨赂 脨陆脨碌 脨驴脨戮脨麓脨麓脨碌脩聙脨露脨赂脨虏脨掳脨碌脩聜 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨戮脨虏脩聥脨碌 脨录脨碌脨陆脨碌脨麓脨露脨碌脩聙脩聥, 脨潞脨戮脩聜脨戮脩聙脩聥脨碌 脨陆脨碌 脨驴脩聙脨碌脨麓脨戮脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨禄脩聫脩聨脩聜 脨驴脨戮脨禄脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脨驴脩聝脩聜脩聦 脨潞 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脩聝.</string>
    <string name="file_does_not_exist_and_cant_be_created">脨陇脨掳脨鹿脨禄 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨掳 脨陆脨碌 脩聛脩聝脩聣脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脩聝脨碌脩聜 脨赂 脨陆脨碌 脨录脨戮脨露脨碌脩聜 脨卤脩聥脩聜脩聦 脩聛脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脨陆脨掳</string>
    <string name="permissions">脨聽脨掳脨路脩聙脨碌脩聢脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="permission_paths_revert">脨聮脨碌脩聙脨陆脩聝脩聜脩聦 脨驴脩聝脩聜脨赂 脨驴脨戮 脩聝脨录脨戮脨禄脩聡脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聨?</string>
    <string name="permission_not_granted">脨聺脨碌脩聜 脩聙脨掳脨路脩聙脨碌脩聢脨碌脨陆脨赂脨鹿</string>
    <string name="sync_to_local_folder_notice">脨聼脩聙脨赂脨录.: 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脩聛脨赂脨陆脩聟脩聙脨戮脨陆脨赂脨路脨掳脩聠脨赂脨赂 脨录脨戮脨鲁脩聝脩聜 脩聙脨掳脨路脨录脨碌脩聣脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脩聥 脨虏 脩聙脨掳脨路脨禄脨赂脩聡脨陆脩聥脩聟 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨掳脩聟. 脨聻脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脨虏脨掳脨鹿脩聜脨碌 脩聧脩聜脨赂 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脩聥, 脨虏脩聥脨卤脨赂脩聙脨掳脩聫 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脩聝 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脨戮脨虏 脨赂脨路 脨聹脨掳脩聙脨潞脨戮脩聙脨掳 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨虏脨戮脨麓脨陆脨赂脨潞脨掳.</string>
    <string name="vertical_alignment">脨聮脩聥脩聙脨掳脨虏脨陆脨赂脨虏脨掳脨陆脨赂脨碌 脨驴脨戮 脨虏脨碌脩聙脩聜脨赂脨潞脨掳脨禄脨赂</string>
    <string name="horizontal_alignment">脨聮脩聥脩聙脨掳脨虏脨陆脨赂脨虏脨掳脨陆脨赂脨碌 脨驴脨戮 脨鲁脨戮脩聙脨赂脨路脨戮脨陆脩聜脨掳脨禄脨赂</string>
    <string name="default_">脨聼脨戮 脩聝脨录脨戮脨禄脩聡脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聨</string>
    <string name="left">脨聼脨戮 脨禄脨碌脨虏脨戮脨录脩聝 脨潞脩聙脨掳脩聨</string>
    <string name="right">脨聼脨戮 脨驴脩聙脨掳脨虏脨戮脨录脩聝 脨潞脩聙脨掳脩聨</string>
    <string name="top">脨聼脨戮 脨虏脨碌脩聙脩聟脨陆脨碌脨录脩聝 脨潞脩聙脨掳脩聨</string>
    <string name="bottom">脨聼脨戮 脨陆脨赂脨路脩聝</string>
    <string name="center">脨娄脨碌脨陆脩聜脩聙</string>
    <string name="actionbutton_spacing">脨聵脨陆脩聜脨碌脩聙脨虏脨掳脨禄 脨录脨碌脨露脨麓脩聝 脨潞脨陆脨戮脨驴脨潞脨掳脨录脨赂 脨麓脨碌脨鹿脩聛脩聜脨虏脨赂脨鹿</string>
    <string name="horizontal_space_between_actionbuttons">脨聯脨戮脩聙脨赂脨路脨戮脨陆脩聜脨掳脨禄脩聦脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脨赂脨陆脩聜脨碌脩聙脨虏脨掳脨禄 脨录脨碌脨露脨麓脩聝 脨潞脨陆脨戮脨驴脨潞脨掳脨录脨赂 脨麓脨碌脨鹿脩聛脩聜脨虏脨赂脨鹿</string>
    <string name="center_text">脨娄脨碌脨陆脩聜脩聙脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜</string>
    <string name="edit_text_in_center_of_screen">脨聽脨掳脨卤脨戮脩聜脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聛 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜脨戮脨录 脨虏 脩聠脨碌脨陆脩聜脩聙脨碌 脩聧脨潞脩聙脨掳脨陆脨掳</string>
    <string name="clipboard">脨聭脩聝脩聞脨碌脩聙 脨戮脨卤脨录脨碌脨陆脨掳</string>
    <string name="select_existing_document">脨聮脩聥脨卤脨碌脩聙脨赂脩聜脨碌 脩聛脩聝脩聣脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脩聝脩聨脩聣脨赂脨鹿 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜</string>
    <string name="select_create_document">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脩聛脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜</string>
    <string name="select_create_folder">脨聮脩聥脨卤脨戮脩聙 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脩聛脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脨陆脨赂脨碌 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="open_source_licenses">脨聸脨赂脩聠脨碌脨陆脨路脨赂脨赂 脩聛 脨戮脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脩聜脩聥脨录 脨赂脩聛脩聟脨戮脨麓脨陆脩聥脨录 脨潞脨戮脨麓脨戮脨录</string>
    <string name="rate_this_app">脨聻脩聠脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="translate">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨虏脨戮脨麓</string>
    <string name="more_info_and_help">脨聰脨戮脨驴脨戮脨禄脨陆脨赂脩聜脨碌脨禄脩聦脨陆脨掳脩聫 脨赂脨陆脩聞脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聠脨赂脩聫 脨赂 脨驴脨戮脨录脨戮脩聣脩聦</string>
    <string name="report_bugs">脨隆脨戮脨戮脨卤脩聣脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨戮脨卤 脨戮脩聢脨赂脨卤脨潞脨掳脩聟</string>
    <string name="do_you_have_a_question_or_problem">脨聲脩聛脩聜脩聦 脨虏脨戮脨驴脩聙脨戮脩聛 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨路脨掳脨录脨碌脩聡脨掳脨陆脨赂脨碌?</string>
    <string name="join_community">脨聼脩聙脨赂脩聛脨戮脨碌脨麓脨赂脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦脩聛脩聫 脨潞 脩聛脨戮脨戮脨卤脩聣脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脩聝</string>
    <string name="bug_reports_suggest_improvements">脨聻脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨戮脩聜脨路脩聥脨虏, 脩聛脨戮脨戮脨卤脩聣脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨戮脨卤 脨戮脩聢脨赂脨卤脨潞脨掳脩聟 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨驴脩聙脨碌脨麓脨禄脨戮脨露脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨赂脨麓脨碌脨赂 脨驴脨戮 脩聝脨禄脩聝脩聡脩聢脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聨</string>
    <string name="help_translating_this_app">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨虏脨碌脩聛脩聜脨赂 脩聧脩聜脨戮 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌 脨陆脨掳 脨麓脩聙脩聝脨鲁脨赂脨碌 脩聫脨路脩聥脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="source_code">脨聵脩聛脩聟脨戮脨麓脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脨潞脨戮脨麓</string>
    <string name="project_license">脨聸脨赂脩聠脨碌脨陆脨路脨赂脩聫 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="contribute_code_to_this_project_anybody_welcome">脨聮脨陆脨碌脩聛脩聜脨赂 脨虏脨潞脨禄脨掳脨麓 脨虏 脨潞脨戮脨麓 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜脨掳. 脨聮脩聛脨碌 脨露脨碌脨禄脨掳脩聨脩聣脨赂脨碌 脨录脨戮脨鲁脩聝脩聜 脩聛脨麓脨碌脨禄脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聧脩聜脨戮, 脨虏 脩聜脨戮脨录 脩聡脨赂脩聛脨禄脨碌 脨赂 脨陆脨戮脨虏脨赂脩聡脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="project_team">脨職脨戮脨录脨掳脨陆脨麓脨掳 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="community">脨隆脨戮脨戮脨卤脩聣脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脨戮</string>
    <string name="contributors_public_add_yourself_description">脨聼脨戮脨潞脨掳脨路 脨赂脨陆脩聞脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聠脨赂脨赂 脨戮脨卤 脩聝脩聡脨掳脩聛脩聜脨陆脨赂脨潞脨掳脩聟. 脨聼脩聙脨碌脨麓脨戮脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脩聦脩聜脨碌 脨赂脨陆脩聞脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聠脨赂脩聨 脨戮 脩聛脨碌脨卤脨碌, 脨碌脩聛脨禄脨赂 脨虏脩聥 脨虏脨陆脨碌脩聛脨禄脨赂 脩聛脨虏脨戮脨鹿 脨虏脨潞脨禄脨掳脨麓 脨虏 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜</string>
    <string name="descending">脨驴脨戮 脩聝脨卤脩聥脨虏脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聨</string>
    <string name="ascending">脨驴脨戮 脨虏脨戮脨路脩聙脨掳脩聛脩聜脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聨</string>
    <string name="disable_spelling_underline">脨聻脩聜脨潞脨禄脩聨脩聡脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨戮脨麓脩聡脩聭脩聙脨潞脨赂脨虏脨掳脨陆脨赂脨碌 脨戮脩聢脨赂脨卤脨戮脨潞</string>
    <string name="spellcheck_keyboard_suggestion_stay_red_underline_vanishes">脨聻脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨戮脨麓脩聛脨潞脨掳脨路脨潞脨赂 脨潞脨禄脨掳脨虏脨赂脨掳脩聜脩聝脩聙脩聥, 脨陆脨戮 脨虏脩聥脨潞脨禄脩聨脩聡脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨潞脩聙脨掳脩聛脨陆脨戮脨碌 脨驴脨戮脨麓脩聡脩聭脩聙脨潞脨赂脨虏脨掳脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="location">脨聹脨碌脩聛脩聜脨戮脨驴脨戮脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="text_lines">脨隆脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="text_characters">脨聴脨陆脨掳脨潞脨戮脨虏</string>
    <string name="text_words">脨隆脨禄脨戮脨虏</string>
    <string name="directory">脨聼脨掳脨驴脨潞脨掳</string>
    <string name="recently_viewed_documents">脨聺脨碌脨麓脨掳脨虏脨陆脨戮 脨戮脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脩聜脩聥脨碌 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脩聥</string>
    <string name="details">脨聼脨戮脨麓脩聙脨戮脨卤脨陆脨戮脩聛脩聜脨赂</string>
    <string name="calendar">脨職脨掳脨禄脨碌脨陆脨麓脨掳脩聙脩聦</string>
    <string name="warning_disallowed_sd_access">脨聮脨陆脨赂脨录脨掳脨陆脨赂脨碌! 脨拢 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨陆脨碌脩聜 脩聙脨掳脨路脩聙脨碌脩聢脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨陆脨掳 脩聛脨戮脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌 脩聧脩聜脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨掳, 脨虏脩聛脨碌 脨赂脨路脨录脨碌脨陆脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨卤脩聝脨麓脩聝脩聜 脨驴脨戮脩聜脨碌脩聙脩聫脨陆脩聥. 脨聺脨碌脩聜 脨虏脨戮脨路脨录脨戮脨露脨陆脨戮脩聛脩聜脨赂 脩聙脨掳脨路脩聙脨碌脩聢脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨卤脨禄脨碌脨录脩聝 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨驴脨戮脨麓脩聜脨虏脨碌脩聙脨麓脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聡脩聜脨戮-脩聜脨戮, Android 脨戮脩聜脨潞脨掳脨路脩聥脨虏脨掳脨碌脩聜 脨虏 脨麓脨戮脩聛脩聜脩聝脨驴脨碌 脨路脨麓脨碌脩聛脩聦.</string>
    <string name="error_picture_selection">脨聵脨路脨戮脨卤脩聙脨掳脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌 脨陆脨碌 脨虏脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脨陆脨陆脨戮.</string>
    <string name="gallery_picture">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨虏 脨鲁脨掳脨禄脨碌脩聙脨碌脨碌</string>
    <string name="camera_picture">脨隆脨麓脨碌脨禄脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聞脨戮脩聜脨戮脨鲁脩聙脨掳脩聞脨赂脩聨</string>
    <string name="enable_undo_and_redo_be_patient">脨聮脨潞脨禄脩聨脩聡脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌 脨戮脩聜脨录脨碌脨陆脩聥 脨赂 脨驴脨戮脨虏脩聜脨戮脩聙脨掳 脨麓脨碌脨鹿脩聛脩聜脨虏脨赂脨鹿. 脨聼脨戮脨麓脩聟脨戮脨麓脨赂脩聜 脩聜脨戮脨禄脩聦脨潞脨戮 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨麓脨虏脨赂脨陆脩聝脩聜脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脨赂脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脨戮脨虏脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聫, 脨驴脩聙脨戮脩聫脨虏脨赂脩聜脨碌 脩聜脨碌脩聙脨驴脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌, 脩聡脩聜脨戮脨卤脩聥 脨陆脨碌 脩聝脨麓脨掳脨禄脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聡脩聜脨戮 脨陆脨赂脨卤脩聝脨麓脩聦 脨虏脨掳脨露脨陆脨戮脨碌. 脨聴脨掳脨潞脩聙脨戮脨鹿脩聜脨碌 脨赂 脨戮脩聜脨潞脩聙脨戮脨鹿脩聜脨碌 脩聙脨碌脨麓脨掳脨潞脩聜脨戮脩聙, 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨戮脩聡脨赂脩聛脩聜脨潞脨赂 脨赂脩聛脩聜脨戮脩聙脨赂脨赂.</string>
    <string name="description">脨聻脨驴脨赂脩聛脨掳脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="edit_picture">脨聵脨路脨录脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨赂脨路脨戮脨卤脩聙脨掳脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="math">脨陇脨戮脩聙脨录脩聝脨禄脩聥</string>
    <string name="enter_yaml_front_matter_attributes_to_show">脨聻脩聜脨戮脨卤脩聙脨掳脨露脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨虏脨虏脨碌脨麓脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聥脨碌 脨掳脩聜脩聙脨赂脨卤脩聝脩聜脩聥 YAML Front Matter 脨虏 脨虏脨碌脩聙脩聟脨陆脨碌脨鹿 脩聡脨掳脩聛脩聜脨赂 脨驴脩聙脨戮脩聛脨录脨掳脩聜脩聙脨赂脨虏脨掳脨碌脨录脩聥脩聟 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脨戮脨虏. 脨聮脨虏脨碌脨麓脨赂脩聜脨碌 脨赂脨录脨碌脨陆脨掳 脨掳脩聜脩聙脨赂脨卤脩聝脩聜脨戮脨虏, 脩聙脨掳脨路脨麓脨碌脨禄脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聥脨碌 脨路脨掳脨驴脩聫脩聜脩聥脨录脨赂. 脨聲脩聛脨禄脨赂 脨驴脩聝脩聛脩聜脨戮 - 脨陆脨赂脩聡脨碌脨鲁脨戮 脨陆脨碌 脨戮脩聜脨戮脨卤脩聙脨掳脨路脨赂脩聜脩聛脩聫. 脨聲脩聛脨禄脨赂 \'*\' - 脨卤脩聝脨麓脩聝脩聜 脨戮脩聜脨戮脨卤脩聙脨掳脨露脨碌脨陆脩聥 脨虏脩聛脨碌. \n\n脨聲脩聛脨禄脨赂 脨掳脩聜脩聙脨赂脨卤脩聝脩聜 脨戮脨驴脩聙脨碌脨麓脨碌脨禄脨碌脨陆 脨虏 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脨碌 (脩聜.脨碌. title: \'Hi\'), 脨赂 脨虏 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脨碌 脩聜脨掳脨潞脨露脨碌 脨碌脩聛脩聜脩聦 {{ post.title }} 脩聜脨戮 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨赂脨路脨戮脨鹿脨麓脩聭脩聜 脨路脨掳脨录脨碌脨陆脨掳. 脨垄脨掳脨潞 脨虏脩聥 脨录脨戮脨露脨碌脩聜脨碌 脩聛脨麓脨碌脨禄脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聛脨虏脨戮脨鹿 脨路脨掳脨鲁脨戮脨禄脨戮脨虏脨戮脨潞 Front Matter.</string>
    <string name="table_of_contents">脨聻脨鲁脨禄脨掳脨虏脨禄脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="miscellaneous">脨聼脩聙脨戮脩聡脨碌脨碌</string>
    <string name="prefer_view">脨聼脩聙脨碌脨麓脨驴脨戮脩聡脨赂脩聜脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨驴脩聙脨戮脩聛脨录脨戮脩聜脩聙</string>
    <string name="no_calendar_app_is_installed">脨聼脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌 脨潞脨掳脨禄脨碌脨陆脨麓脨掳脩聙脩聫 脨陆脨碌 脩聝脩聛脩聜脨掳脨陆脨戮脨虏脨禄脨碌脨陆脨戮!</string>
    <string name="popular_documents">脨搂脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聥脨碌 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脩聥</string>
    <string name="color">脨娄脨虏脨碌脩聜</string>
    <string name="basic_color_scheme">脨聻脩聛脨陆脨戮脨虏脨陆脨掳脩聫 脨驴脨掳脨禄脨赂脩聜脩聙脨掳</string>
    <string name="background_foreground_color_in_editor_works_dark_light">脨聵脨路脨录脨碌脨陆脩聫脨碌脩聜 脩聞脨戮脨陆脨戮脨虏脩聥脨鹿 脨赂 脨戮脩聛脨陆脨戮脨虏脨陆脨戮脨鹿 脩聠脨虏脨碌脩聜 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜脨戮脨虏脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脩聙脨碌脨麓脨掳脨潞脩聜脨戮脩聙脨掳. 脨聼脩聙脨赂脩聛脨驴脨戮脩聛脨掳脨卤脨禄脨赂脨虏脨掳脨碌脩聜脩聛脩聫 脨潞 脩聜脩聭脨录脨陆脨戮脨鹿 脨赂 脩聛脨虏脨碌脩聜脨禄脨戮脨鹿 脩聜脨碌脨录脨碌 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫. 脨娄脨虏脨碌脩聜 脨虏脩聥脨麓脨碌脨禄脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜脨掳 脨戮脩聛脩聜脨掳脩聭脩聜脩聛脩聫 脩聜脨掳脨潞脨赂脨录 脨露脨碌.</string>
    <string name="preset">脨篓脨掳脨卤脨禄脨戮脨陆</string>
    <string name="foreground">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨麓脨陆脨赂脨鹿 脨驴脨禄脨掳脨陆</string>
    <string name="background">脨陇脨戮脨陆</string>
    <string name="set_foreground_or_background_color_hexcolor_also_possible">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聠脨虏脨碌脩聜 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜脨掳 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脩聞脨戮脨陆脨掳? 脨聹脨戮脨露脨陆脨戮 脨赂脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聜脨掳脨潞脨露脨碌 脩聠脨虏脨碌脩聜脨戮脨虏脨戮脨鹿 hex-脨潞脨戮脨麓.</string>
    <string name="type">脨垄脨赂脨驴</string>
    <string name="folder">脨聼脨掳脨驴脨潞脨掳</string>
    <string name="folder_is_created_without_extension">芒聙聰 脨聼脨掳脨驴脨潞脨掳 脩聛脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脩聭脩聜脩聛脩聫 脨卤脨碌脨路 脩聙脨掳脩聛脩聢脨赂脩聙脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="keep_existing_file">芒聙聰 脨陇脨掳脨鹿脨禄脩聥 脨赂 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨赂 脨陆脨碌 脨驴脨碌脩聙脨碌脨路脨掳脨驴脨赂脩聛脩聥脨虏脨掳脩聨脩聜脩聛脩聫</string>
    <string name="multiple_windows">脨聺脨碌脩聛脨潞脨戮脨禄脩聦脨潞脨戮 脨戮脨潞脨戮脨陆</string>
    <string name="font">脨篓脩聙脨赂脩聞脩聜</string>
    <string name="open_new_documents_always_in_new_window">脨聻脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脩聥 脨虏 脨戮脩聜脨麓脨碌脨禄脩聦脨陆脩聥脩聟 脨戮脨潞脨陆脨掳脩聟. 脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨潞脨禄脩聨脩聡脨掳脨鹿脩聜脨碌脩聛脩聦 脨录脨碌脨露脨麓脩聝 脨陆脨赂脨录脨赂 脩聛 脨驴脨戮脨录脨戮脩聣脩聦脩聨 脨潞脨陆脨戮脨驴脨潞脨赂 脗芦脨聻脨卤脨路脨戮脩聙脗禄 脨陆脨掳 脩聝脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脩聛脩聜脨虏脨碌</string>
    <string name="enter_or_select_format">脨聮脨虏脨碌脨麓脨赂脩聜脨碌 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨虏脩聥脨卤脨碌脩聙脨赂脩聜脨碌 脩聞脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜</string>
    <string name="pick_date">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聝</string>
    <string name="pick_time">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨虏脩聙脨碌脨录脩聫</string>
    <string name="get_format_instead_date_or_time">脨聼脨戮脨禄脩聝脩聡脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聞脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜 脨虏脨录脨碌脩聛脩聜脨戮 脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聥 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨虏脩聙脨碌脨录脨碌脨陆脨赂</string>
    <string name="use_current_date_and_time">脨聮脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聝 脨赂 脨虏脩聙脨碌脨录脩聫</string>
    <string name="result">脨聽脨碌脨路脩聝脨禄脩聦脩聜脨掳脩聜</string>
    <string name="just_time">脨垄脨戮脨禄脩聦脨潞脨戮 脨虏脩聙脨碌脨录脩聫</string>
    <string name="just_date">脨垄脨戮脨禄脩聦脨潞脨戮 脨麓脨掳脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="last_used">脨聼脨戮脩聛脨禄脨碌脨麓脨陆脨赂脨鹿 脨赂脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脨戮脨虏脨掳脨陆脨陆脩聥脨鹿</string>
    <string name="my_note">脨录脨戮脩聫 脨路脨掳脨录脨碌脩聜脨潞脨掳</string>
    <string name="close">脨聴脨掳脨潞脩聙脩聥脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="cancel">脨聻脩聜脨录脨碌脨陆脨掳</string>
    <string name="app_start_tab">脨聺脨掳脩聡脨掳脨禄脩聦脨陆脨掳脩聫 脨虏脨潞脨禄脨掳脨麓脨潞脨掳</string>
    <string name="tab_to_select_at_start">脨聺脨掳脩聡脨掳脨禄脩聦脨陆脨掳脩聫 脨虏脨潞脨禄脨掳脨麓脨潞脨掳 脨驴脩聙脨赂 脨路脨掳脨驴脩聝脩聛脨潞脨碌 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="swipe_to_change_mode">脨隆脨录脨掳脩聟脨陆脨赂脩聜脨碌 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨赂脨路脨录脨碌脨陆脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脩聙脨碌脨露脨赂脨录脨掳</string>
    <string name="swipe_to_change_to_edit_or_view_mode">脨隆脨录脨掳脩聟脨陆脨赂脩聜脨碌 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨驴脨碌脩聙脨碌脩聟脨戮脨麓脨掳 脨录脨碌脨露脨麓脩聝 脩聙脨碌脨露脨赂脨录脨戮脨录 脩聙脨碌脨麓脨掳脨潞脩聜脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨赂 脨驴脩聙脨戮脩聛脨录脨戮脩聜脩聙脨掳 (脨陆脨掳 脩聙脨碌脨露脨赂脨录, 脨驴脩聙脨戮脩聜脨赂脨虏脨戮脨驴脨戮脨禄脨戮脨露脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聝脩聣脨碌脨录脩聝)</string>
    <string name="folder_first">脨聼脨掳脨驴脨潞脨赂 脨虏脨虏脨碌脩聙脩聟脩聝</string>
    <string name="go_to">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨鹿脩聜脨赂 脨潞</string>
    <string name="appdata_public">AppData (public)</string>
    <string name="appdata_private">AppData (private)</string>
    <string name="appdata_sdcard">AppData (SD-脨潞脨掳脩聙脩聜脨掳)</string>
    <string name="internal_storage">脨聮脨陆脩聝脩聜脩聙脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聫脩聫 脨驴脨掳脨录脩聫脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="open_the_document_from_main_view">脨聮脩聥 脨录脨戮脨露脨碌脩聜脨碌 脨戮脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脩聜脩聦 脨麓脨戮脨潞脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜 脨赂脨路 脨鲁脨禄脨掳脨虏脨陆脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脨虏脨赂脨麓脨掳 脨虏脨陆脨赂脨路脩聝, 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨戮脨虏脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聝脨路脨碌脩聙脨掳 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨禄脨掳脩聝脨陆脩聡脨碌脩聙脨掳. 脨垄脨掳脨潞脨露脨碌 脨碌脩聛脩聜脩聦 脨虏脨戮脨路脨录脨戮脨露脨陆脨戮脩聛脩聜脩聦 脨麓脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜, 脩聙脨掳脨路脨麓脨碌脨禄脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脨虏 Portal.</string>
    <string name="notebook_is_the_home_of_your_files">脨聭脨禄脨戮脨潞脨陆脨戮脩聜 芒聙聰 脩聧脩聜脨戮 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨掳, 脨潞脨戮脩聜脨戮脩聙脩聝脩聨 Portal 脨戮脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脨虏脨掳脨碌脩聜 脨虏 脨戮脨卤脨戮脨路脩聙脨碌脨虏脨掳脩聜脨碌脨禄脨碌 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨戮脨虏 脨驴脩聙脨赂 脨路脨掳脨驴脩聝脩聛脨潞脨碌. 脨颅脩聜脨戮 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨掳 脨驴脨戮 脩聝脨录脨戮脨禄脩聡脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聨 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨虏脨掳脩聢脨赂脩聟 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨戮脨虏.</string>
    <string name="quicknote_is_the_fastest_option_to_write_down_notes">QuickNote 脨驴脨戮脨录脨戮脨鲁脨掳脨碌脩聜 脨卤脩聥脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮 脨麓脨碌脨禄脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨路脨掳脨录脨碌脩聜脨潞脨赂. 脨颅脩聜脨戮 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄 脨虏 脩聞脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜脨碌 Markdown, 脨驴脩聝脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨戮 脩聝脨录脨戮脨禄脩聡脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聨: &gt;Notebook/QuickNote.md&lt;. 脨聮脩聥 脨录脨戮脨露脨碌脩聜脨碌 脨赂脨路脨录脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨驴脩聝脩聜脩聦 脨虏 脨陆脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脨潞脨掳脩聟.</string>
    <string name="todo_is_the_easiest_way_">脨拢脨驴脩聙脨掳脨虏脨禄脩聫脨鹿脩聜脨碌 脨路脨掳脨麓脨掳脩聡脨掳脨录脨赂 脩聛 脨驴脨戮脨录脨戮脩聣脩聦脩聨 ToDo. 脨颅脩聜脨戮 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄 脨虏 脩聞脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜脨碌 todo.txt, 脨驴脩聝脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨戮 脩聝脨录脨戮脨禄脩聡脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聨: &gt;Notebook/todo.txt&lt;. 脨聮脩聥 脨录脨戮脨露脨碌脩聜脨碌 脨赂脨路脨录脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨驴脩聝脩聜脩聦 脨虏 脨陆脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脨潞脨掳脩聟.</string>
    <string name="navigationbar_color">脨娄脨虏脨碌脩聜 脨驴脨掳脨陆脨碌脨禄脨赂 脨陆脨掳脨虏脨赂脨鲁脨掳脩聠脨赂脨赂</string>
    <string name="black">脨搂脩聭脩聙脨陆脩聥脨鹿</string>
    <string name="white">脨聭脨碌脨禄脩聥脨鹿</string>
    <string name="view">脨聼脩聙脨戮脩聛脨录脨戮脩聜脩聙</string>
    <string name="view_mode">脨聽脨碌脨露脨赂脨录 脨驴脩聙脨戮脩聛脨录脨戮脩聜脩聙脨掳</string>
    <string name="edit_mode">脨聽脨碌脨露脨赂脨录 脩聙脨碌脨麓脨掳脨潞脩聜脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="mount_storage">脨聼脨戮脨麓脨潞脨禄脩聨脩聡脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌 脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脨赂脨禄脨赂脩聣脨掳</string>
    <string name="application_needs_access_to_storage_mount_it">脨聰脨禄脩聫 脨麓脨戮脩聛脩聜脩聝脨驴脨掳 脨潞 脩聧脩聜脨戮脨录脩聝 脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脨赂脨禄脨赂脩聣脩聝 脩聜脩聙脨碌脨卤脩聝脨碌脩聜脩聛脩聫 脩聙脨掳脨路脩聙脨碌脩聢脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌. 脨聼脨戮脨麓脨潞脨禄脩聨脩聡脨赂脩聜脨碌 脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脨赂脨禄脨赂脩聣脨碌 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨驴脩聙脨碌脨麓脨戮脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨禄脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨麓脨戮脩聛脩聜脩聝脨驴脨掳. 脨聼脨戮脨麓脩聜脨虏脨碌脩聙脨麓脨赂脩聜脨碌 脩聧脩聜脨戮脩聜 脨麓脨赂脨掳脨禄脨戮脨鲁, 脩聡脩聜脨戮脨卤脩聥 脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聝脩聡脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨虏脩聛脨驴脨禄脩聥脨虏脨掳脩聨脩聣脨碌脨碌 脨戮脨潞脨陆脨戮. 脨聮脩聥脨卤脨碌脩聙脨赂脩聜脨碌 脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脨赂脨禄脨赂脩聣脨碌 脨赂 脨陆脨掳脨露脨录脨赂脩聜脨碌 脨潞脨陆脨戮脨驴脨潞脩聝 \"脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脩聜脩聦\".</string>
    <string name="share_into">脨聼脨戮脨麓脨碌脨禄脨赂脩聜脩聦脩聛脩聫 脨虏</string>
    <string name="favourite">脨聵脨路脨卤脩聙脨掳脨陆脨陆脨戮脨碌</string>
    <string name="favourites">脨聵脨路脨卤脩聙脨掳脨陆脨陆脩聥脨碌</string>
    <string name="please_wait">脨聼脨戮脨麓脨戮脨露脨麓脨赂脩聜脨碌</string>
    <string name="app_start_folder">脨聺脨掳脩聡脨掳脨禄脩聦脨陆脨掳脩聫 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨掳</string>
    <string name="tab_width">脨篓脨赂脩聙脨赂脨陆脨掳 脩聜脨掳脨卤脩聝脨禄脩聫脩聠脨赂脨赂</string>
    <string name="amount_of_space_for_tab">脨職脨戮脨禄脨赂脩聡脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脨戮 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨卤脨碌脨禄脨戮脨虏 脨虏 脨戮脩聜脩聛脩聜脩聝脨驴脨碌</string>
    <string name="selected_file_may_be_a_textfile_want_to_open_in_editor">脨聮脩聥脨卤脨碌脩聙脨赂脩聜脨碌 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜脨戮脨虏脩聥脨鹿 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄. 脨聮脩聥 脩聟脨戮脩聜脨赂脩聜脨碌 脨戮脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脩聜脩聦 脨碌脨鲁脨戮 脨虏 脩聙脨碌脨麓脨掳脨潞脩聜脨戮脩聙脨碌 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨虏 脨麓脩聙脩聝脨鲁脨戮脨录 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨赂? \n\n脨聺脨碌 脨驴脩聥脩聜脨掳脨鹿脩聜脨碌脩聛脩聦 脨戮脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨卤脨赂脨陆脨掳脩聙脨陆脩聥脨碌 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脩聥. 脨聲脩聛脨禄脨赂 脨虏脩聥 脨陆脨碌 脩聝脨虏脨碌脩聙脨碌脨陆脩聥, 脨戮脩聜脨潞脩聙脨戮脨鹿脩聜脨碌 脨麓脩聙脩聝脨鲁脨赂脨录 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌脨录.</string>
    <string name="list_in_recent_files">脨聼脨戮脨潞脨掳脨路脩聥脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨虏 脨陆脨碌脨麓脨掳脨虏脨陆脨赂脩聟 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨掳脩聟</string>
    <string name="reload">脨聻脨卤脨陆脨戮脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="wrap_words">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨陆脨戮脩聛脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聛脨禄脨戮脨虏脨掳</string>
    <string name="line_numbers">脨聺脩聝脨录脨碌脩聙脨掳脩聠脨赂脩聫 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞</string>
    <string name="soft_break_if_not_fit_to_width_else_enable_horizontal_scrolling">脨聮脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨禄脩聫脩聜脩聦 脨录脩聫脨鲁脨潞脨赂脨碌 脨驴脨碌脩聙脨碌脨陆脨戮脩聛脩聥 脨虏脨录脨碌脩聛脩聜脨戮 脨戮脩聜脨戮脨卤脩聙脨掳脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨驴脨戮脨禄脨路脩聝脨陆脨潞脨掳 脨鲁脨戮脩聙脨赂脨路脨戮脨陆脩聜脨掳脨禄脩聦脨陆脨戮脨鹿 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨潞脩聙脩聝脩聜脨潞脨赂, 脨潞脨戮脨鲁脨麓脨掳 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜 脨陆脨碌 脨驴脨戮脨录脨碌脩聣脨掳脨碌脩聜脩聛脩聫 脨驴脨戮 脩聢脨赂脩聙脨赂脨陆脨碌 脨陆脨掳 脩聧脨潞脩聙脨掳脨陆脨碌.</string>
    <string name="recursive_search_in_location">脨聽脨碌脨潞脩聝脩聙脩聛脨赂脨虏脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脨驴脨戮脨赂脩聛脨潞 脨虏 %s</string>
    <string name="always_open_with_this_app">脨聮脩聛脨碌脨鲁脨麓脨掳 脨戮脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨虏 脩聧脩聜脨戮脨录 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨赂</string>
    <string name="always_open_files_with_this_app_when_list_contains_file_extension">脨聲脩聛脨禄脨赂 脩聙脨掳脩聛脩聢脨赂脩聙脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨掳 脨碌脩聛脩聜脩聦 脨虏 脩聛脨驴脨赂脩聛脨潞脨碌, 脨虏脩聛脨碌脨鲁脨麓脨掳 脨卤脩聝脨麓脨碌脩聜 脨戮脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨碌脨鲁脨戮 脨虏 Portal. 脨職 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨录脨碌脩聙脩聝, 脨碌脩聛脨禄脨赂 脨虏脩聥 脩聟脨戮脩聜脨赂脩聜脨碌 脩聙脨碌脨麓脨掳脨潞脩聜脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脩聥 脨卤脨碌脨路 脩聙脨掳脩聛脩聢脨赂脩聙脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨赂 脨虏脨碌脨卤-脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脩聥, 脨虏脨虏脨碌脨麓脨赂脩聜脨碌 \'None, .html, .css, .js\'.</string>
    <string name="open_file_with">脨聻脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脩聜脩聦 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄</string>
    <string name="rotate">脨聼脨戮脨虏脨戮脩聙脨戮脩聜</string>
    <string name="template">脨篓脨掳脨卤脨禄脨戮脨陆</string>
    <string name="send_debug_log">脨聻脩聜脨驴脩聙脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨露脩聝脩聙脨陆脨掳脨禄 脨戮脩聜脨禄脨掳脨麓脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="print_pdf">脨聽脨掳脩聛脨驴脨碌脩聡脨掳脩聜脨掳脩聜脩聦 / PDF</string>
    <string name="bigger_headings">脨拢脨虏脨碌脨禄脨赂脩聡脨赂脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨路脨掳脨鲁脨戮脨禄脨戮脨虏脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="increase_text_size_of_headings_according_to_level">脨拢脨虏脨碌脨禄脨赂脩聡脨赂脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聙脨掳脨路脨录脨碌脩聙 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜脨掳 脨路脨掳脨鲁脨戮脨禄脨戮脨虏脨潞脨戮脨虏 脨虏 脩聛脨戮脨戮脩聜脨虏脨碌脩聜脩聛脩聜脨虏脨赂脨赂 脩聛 脩聝脩聙脨戮脨虏脨陆脨碌脨录 (# h1, ## h2, ### h3芒聙娄)</string>
    <string name="current">脨垄脨碌脨潞脩聝脩聣脨赂脨鹿</string>
    <string name="record_audio">脨聴脨掳脨驴脨赂脩聛脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨聬脩聝脨麓脨赂脨戮</string>
    <string name="attach">脨聼脩聙脨赂脨潞脩聙脨碌脨驴脨赂脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="attachment">脨聮脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="copy_file">脨職脨戮脨驴脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄</string>
    <string name="page">脨隆脩聜脩聙脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聠脨掳</string>
    <string name="experimental_features">脨颅脨潞脩聛脨驴脨碌脩聙脨赂脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脨掳脨禄脩聦脨陆脩聥脨碌 脩聞脩聝脨陆脨潞脩聠脨赂脨赂</string>
    <string name="tools">脨聵脨陆脩聛脩聜脩聙脩聝脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脩聥</string>
    <string name="reading">脨搂脩聜脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="read">脨搂脨赂脩聜脨掳脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="table">脨垄脨掳脨卤脨禄脨赂脩聠脨掳</string>
    <string name="how_much_columns_press_table_button_long_to_start_table">脨隆脨潞脨戮脨禄脩聦脨潞脨戮 脨潞脨戮脨禄脨戮脨陆脨戮脨潞? 脨聳脨录脨赂脩聜脨碌 脨潞脨陆脨戮脨驴脨潞脩聝 脩聜脨掳脨卤脨禄脨赂脩聠脩聥 脨麓脨戮脨禄脨鲁脨戮, 脩聡脩聜脨戮脨卤脩聥 脨陆脨掳脩聡脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聜脨掳脨卤脨禄脨赂脩聠脩聝 (脨虏脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨路脨掳脨鲁脨戮脨禄脨戮脨虏脨戮脨潞), 脨陆脨掳脨露脨录脨赂脩聜脨碌 脨潞脨戮脩聙脨戮脩聜脨潞脨戮 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨麓脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨禄脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脨赂.</string>
    <string name="example_of_a_markdown_table">脨聼脩聙脨赂脨录脨碌脩聙 Markdown-脩聜脨掳脨卤脨禄脨赂脩聠脩聥</string>
    <string name="delete_lines">脨拢脨麓脨掳脨禄脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="duplicate_lines">脨聰脩聝脨卤脨禄脨赂 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="unordered_list">脨聺脨碌脩聝脨驴脨戮脩聙脩聫脨麓脨戮脩聡脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脩聛脨驴脨赂脩聛脨戮脨潞</string>
    <string name="ordered_list">脨聺脩聝脨录脨碌脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脨陆脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脩聛脨驴脨赂脩聛脨戮脨潞</string>
    <string name="check_list">脨職脨戮脨陆脩聜脩聙脨戮脨禄脩聦脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脩聛脨驴脨赂脩聛脨戮脨潞</string>
    <string name="open_link">脨聻脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脩聜脩聦 脩聛脩聛脩聥脨禄脨潞脩聝</string>
    <string name="common_color_picker">脨聮脩聥脨卤脨戮脩聙 脩聠脨虏脨碌脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="date_and_time">脨聰脨掳脩聜脨掳 脨赂 脨虏脩聙脨碌脨录脩聫</string>
    <string name="jump_to_bottom">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨鹿脩聜脨赂 脨虏 脨潞脨戮脨陆脨碌脩聠</string>
    <string name="quote">脨娄脨赂脩聜脨掳脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="heading">脨聴脨掳脨鲁脨戮脨禄脨戮脨虏脨戮脨潞</string>
    <string name="heading_1">脨聴脨掳脨鲁脨戮脨禄脨戮脨虏脨戮脨潞 1</string>
    <string name="heading_2">脨聴脨掳脨鲁脨戮脨禄脨戮脨虏脨戮脨潞 2</string>
    <string name="heading_3">脨聴脨掳脨鲁脨戮脨禄脨戮脨虏脨戮脨潞 3</string>
    <string name="heading_4">脨聴脨掳脨鲁脨戮脨禄脨戮脨虏脨戮脨潞 4</string>
    <string name="heading_5">脨聴脨掳脨鲁脨戮脨禄脨戮脨虏脨戮脨潞 5</string>
    <string name="heading_6">脨聴脨掳脨鲁脨戮脨禄脨戮脨虏脨戮脨潞 6</string>
    <string name="bold">脨聳脨赂脩聙脨陆脩聥脨鹿</string>
    <string name="italic">脨職脩聝脩聙脩聛脨赂脨虏</string>
    <string name="highlighted">脨聮脩聥脨麓脨碌脨禄脨碌脨陆脨戮</string>
    <string name="strikeout">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脩聡脨碌脩聙脨潞脨陆脩聝脩聜脩聥脨鹿</string>
    <string name="inline_code">脨聹脨戮脨陆脨戮脩聢脨赂脩聙脨赂脨陆脨陆脩聥脨鹿</string>
    <string name="horizontal_line">脨聯脨戮脩聙脨赂脨路脨戮脨陆脩聜脨掳脨禄脩聦脨陆脨掳脩聫 脨禄脨赂脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="toggle_done">脨隆脨录脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聛脩聜脨掳脩聜脩聝脩聛</string>
    <string name="link_color">脨娄脨虏脨碌脩聜 脩聛脩聛脩聥脨禄脨戮脨潞</string>
    <string name="add_context">脨聰脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨潞脨戮脨陆脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜</string>
    <string name="add_project">脨聰脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜</string>
    <string name="archive_completed_tasks">脨聬脩聙脩聟脨赂脨虏脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨路脨掳脨虏脨碌脩聙脩聢脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聥脨碌 脨路脨掳脨麓脨掳脩聡脨赂</string>
    <string name="create_new_file_or_folder">脨隆脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨陆脨戮脨虏脩聥脨鹿 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脩聝</string>
    <string name="choose_format">脨聮脩聥脨卤脨碌脩聙脨赂脩聜脨碌 脩聞脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜</string>
    <string name="clear_selection">脨隆脨卤脩聙脨戮脩聛脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨虏脩聥脨卤脨戮脩聙</string>
    <string name="selected">脨聮脩聥脨卤脩聙脨掳脨陆脨戮</string>
    <string name="back">脨聺脨掳脨路脨掳脨麓</string>
    <string name="expand_collapse">脨聽脨掳脨路脨虏脨碌脩聙脨陆脩聝脩聜脩聦 / 脨隆脨虏脨碌脩聙脨陆脩聝脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="essential">脨聻脩聛脨陆脨戮脨虏脨陆脨戮脨碌</string>
    <string name="append_human_readable_uuid_to_new_tasks">脨聰脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聡脨碌脨禄脨戮脨虏脨碌脨潞脨戮脩聡脨赂脩聜脨掳脨碌脨录脩聥脨鹿 UUID 脨潞 脨陆脨戮脨虏脩聥脨录 脨路脨掳脨麓脨掳脩聡脨掳脨录</string>
    <string name="action_order">脨聼脨戮脩聙脩聫脨麓脨戮脨潞 脨麓脨碌脨鹿脩聛脩聜脨虏脨赂脨鹿</string>
    <string name="toggle_action_visibility">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨潞脨禄脩聨脩聡脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨虏脨赂脨麓脨赂脨录脨戮脩聛脩聜脩聦 脨戮脨驴脨碌脩聙脨掳脩聠脨赂脨赂</string>
    <string name="load_default_settings">脨聴脨掳脨鲁脩聙脩聝脨路脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨陆脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脨潞脨赂 脨驴脨戮 脩聝脨录脨戮脨禄脩聡脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聨</string>
    <string name="drag">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脩聜脨掳脩聣脨赂脩聜脨碌</string>
    <string name="created">脨隆脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脨陆脨戮</string>
    <string name="file_encryption_password">脨聼脨掳脩聙脨戮脨禄脩聦 脩聢脨赂脩聞脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聫 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨掳</string>
    <string name="no_password_set_cannot_encrypt_decrypt">脨聼脨掳脩聙脨戮脨禄脩聦 脨陆脨碌 脩聝脩聛脩聜脨掳脨陆脨戮脨虏脨禄脨碌脨陆, 脨陆脨碌 脨录脨戮脨鲁脩聝 脨路脨掳脩聢脨赂脩聞脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脩聙脨掳脩聛脩聢脨赂脩聞脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦.\n脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨鹿脨麓脨赂脩聜脨碌 脨虏 脨聺脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脨潞脨赂 -&gt; 脨聻脨卤脩聣脨赂脨碌 -&gt; 脨聼脨掳脩聙脨戮脨禄脩聦 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脩聝脩聛脩聜脨掳脨陆脨戮脨虏脨潞脨赂 脨驴脨掳脩聙脨戮脨禄脩聫.</string>
    <string name="encrypt_file_content">脨篓脨赂脩聞脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聛脨戮脨麓脨碌脩聙脨露脨赂脨录脨戮脨碌 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨掳</string>
    <string name="utf8_with_bom">UTF-8 脩聛 BOM</string>
    <string name="could_not_encrypt_file_content_the_file_was_not_saved">脨聺脨碌 脩聝脨麓脨掳脨禄脨戮脩聛脩聦 脨路脨掳脩聢脨赂脩聞脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聛脨戮脨麓脨碌脩聙脨露脨赂脨录脨戮脨碌 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨掳. 脨陇脨掳脨鹿脨禄 脨陆脨碌 脨卤脩聥脨禄 脩聛脨戮脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脨碌脨陆.</string>
    <string name="could_not_decrypt_file_content_wrong_password_or_is_the_file_maybe_not_encrypted">脨聺脨碌 脩聝脨麓脨掳脨禄脨戮脩聛脩聦 脩聙脨掳脩聛脩聢脨赂脩聞脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聛脨戮脨麓脨碌脩聙脨露脨赂脨录脨戮脨碌 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨掳. 脨聵脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脩聝脨碌脩聜脨碌 脨禄脨赂 脨虏脩聥 脨虏脨碌脩聙脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脨驴脨掳脩聙脨戮脨禄脩聦? 脨陇脨掳脨鹿脨禄 脨麓脨碌脨鹿脩聛脩聜脨虏脨赂脩聜脨碌脨禄脩聦脨陆脨戮 脨卤脩聥脨禄 脨路脨掳脩聢脨赂脩聞脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脨陆 Portal鈥檚 AES?</string>
    <string name="password_already_set_setting_a_new_password_will_overwrite">脨聼脨掳脩聙脨戮脨禄脩聦 脩聝脨露脨碌 脩聝脩聛脩聜脨掳脨陆脨戮脨虏脨禄脨碌脨陆. 脨拢脩聛脩聜脨掳脨陆脨戮脨虏脨潞脨掳 脨陆脨戮脨虏脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脨驴脨掳脩聙脨戮脨禄脩聫 脨驴脨碌脩聙脨碌脨路脨掳脨驴脨赂脩聢脨碌脩聜 脩聛脩聝脩聣脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脩聝脩聨脩聣脨赂脨鹿 脨驴脨掳脩聙脨戮脨禄脩聦, 脨赂 脨虏脩聥 脨卤脨戮脨禄脩聦脩聢脨碌 脨陆脨碌 脩聛脨录脨戮脨露脨碌脩聜脨碌 脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聝脩聡脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨麓脨戮脩聛脩聜脩聝脨驴 脨潞 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨掳脨录 脨虏 脩聛脨禄脩聝脩聡脨掳脨碌, 脨碌脩聛脨禄脨赂 脨虏脩聥 脨路脨掳脨卤脩聝脨麓脨碌脩聜脨碌 脨驴脨掳脩聙脨戮脨禄脩聦.</string>
    <string name="code_block">脨聭脨禄脨戮脨潞 脨潞脨戮脨麓脨掳</string>
    <string name="add_completion_date">脨聰脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聝 脨路脨掳脨虏脨碌脩聙脩聢脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="add_completion_date_for_todos_when_marking_them_as_done">脨聰脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨禄脩聫脩聜脩聦 脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聝 脨路脨掳脨虏脨碌脩聙脩聢脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨路脨掳脨麓脨掳脩聡 脨驴脩聙脨赂 脨驴脨戮脨录脨碌脩聜脨潞脨碌 脨赂脩聟 脨潞脨掳脨潞 脨虏脩聥脨驴脨戮脨禄脨陆脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聥脩聟</string>
    <string name="file_description_format">脨陇脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜 脨戮脨驴脨赂脩聛脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聫 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨掳</string>
    <string name="file_description_format_dialog">脨陇脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜 脨戮脨驴脨赂脩聛脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨潞脨掳脨露脨麓脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨掳 脨虏 脨戮脨卤脨戮脨路脩聙脨碌脨虏脨掳脩聜脨碌脨禄脨碌. 脨隆脨禄脨碌脨麓脩聝脨鹿脩聜脨碌 脨驴脩聙脨掳脨虏脨赂脨禄脨掳脨录 SimpleDateFormat Android, 脨麓脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨赂脨虏 FS 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨戮脩聜脨戮脨卤脩聙脨掳脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脩聙脨掳脨路脨录脨碌脩聙脨掳 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨掳. 脨聻脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脩聦脩聜脨碌 脨驴脩聝脩聛脩聜脩聥脨录, 脩聡脩聜脨戮脨卤脩聥 脨赂脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聞脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜 脨驴脨戮 脩聝脨录脨戮脨禄脩聡脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聨 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨虏脨掳脩聢脨碌脨鹿 脨禄脨戮脨潞脨掳脨禄脨赂.\n\n脨聼脩聙脨赂脨录脨碌脩聙 脨虏脨虏脨戮脨麓脨掳:\nFS yyyy MMM dd hh:mm:ss aa\n脨陇脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜 脨虏脩聥脨虏脨戮脨麓脨掳:\n30KB 2020 脨聹脨掳脩聙 20 11:24:52 PM</string>
    <string name="loading_default_value">脨聴脨掳脨鲁脩聙脩聝脨路脨潞脨掳 脨路脨陆脨掳脩聡脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨驴脨戮 脩聝脨录脨戮脨禄脩聡脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聨</string>
    <string name="file_settings">脨聺脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脨潞脨赂 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨掳</string>
    <string name="search_and_replace">脨聼脨戮脨赂脩聛脨潞 / 脨聴脨掳脨录脨碌脨陆脨掳</string>
    <string name="search_for">脨聵脩聛脨潞脨掳脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="replace_with">脨聴脨掳脨录脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨陆脨掳</string>
    <string name="replace_once">脨聴脨掳脨录脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦 (1)</string>
    <string name="replace_all">脨聴脨掳脨录脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨虏脩聛脨碌</string>
    <string name="matches">脨隆脨戮脨虏脨驴脨掳脨麓脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="search_replace_pattern_error_message">脨聼脨戮脨赂脩聛脨潞 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脨路脨掳脨录脨碌脨陆脨掳 脩聢脨掳脨卤脨禄脨戮脨陆脨掳.</string>
    <string name="backup_settings">脨隆脨戮脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨陆脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="restore_settings">脨聮脨戮脩聛脩聛脩聜脨掳脨陆脨戮脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨陆脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脨潞脨赂</string>
    <string name="failed_to_create_backup">脨聺脨碌 脩聝脨麓脨掳脨禄脨戮脩聛脩聦 脩聛脨戮脨路脨麓脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聙脨碌脨路脨碌脩聙脨虏脨陆脩聝脩聨 脨潞脨戮脨驴脨赂脩聨</string>
    <string name="export_settings_to_json_file">脨颅脨潞脩聛脨驴脨戮脩聙脩聜 脨陆脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞 脨虏 json 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄</string>
    <string name="import_settings_from_backup_json_file_on_success_the_app_is_restarted">脨聵脨录脨驴脨戮脩聙脩聜 脨陆脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞 脨赂脨路 脩聙脨碌脨路脨碌脩聙脨虏脨陆脨戮脨鹿 脨潞脨戮脨驴脨赂脨赂 json 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脨掳. 脨聼脩聙脨赂 脩聝脩聛脨驴脨碌脩聢脨陆脨戮脨录 脨路脨掳脨虏脨碌脩聙脩聢脨碌脨陆脨赂脨赂 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌 脨驴脨碌脩聙脨碌脨路脨掳脨驴脩聝脩聛脨潞脨掳脨碌脩聜脩聛脩聫.</string>
    <string name="failed_to_restore_settings_from_backup">脨聺脨碌 脩聝脨麓脨掳脨禄脨戮脩聛脩聦 脨虏脨戮脩聛脩聛脩聜脨掳脨陆脨戮脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨陆脨掳脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨鹿脨潞脨赂 脨赂脨路 脩聙脨碌脨路脨碌脩聙脨虏脨陆脨戮脨鹿 脨潞脨戮脨驴脨赂脨赂</string>
    <string name="newline_is_new_paragraph">Newline = 脨陆脨戮脨虏脩聥脨鹿 脨掳脨卤脨路脨掳脩聠</string>
    <string name="search_in_content">脨聼脨戮脨赂脩聛脨潞 脨驴脨戮 脩聛脨戮脨麓脨碌脩聙脨露脨赂脨录脨戮脨录脩聝</string>
    <string name="max_search_depth">脨聯脨禄脩聝脨卤脨赂脨陆脨掳 脨驴脨戮脨赂脩聛脨潞脨掳</string>
    <string name="ignore_list">脨聵脨鲁脨陆脨戮脩聙脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="do_not_search_specified_files_and_folders">脨聺脨碌 脨赂脩聛脨潞脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聝脨潞脨掳脨路脨掳脨陆脨陆脩聥脨碌 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄脩聥 脨赂 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨赂.\n脨聵脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脩聝脨鹿脩聜脨碌 脨陆脨戮脨虏脩聝脩聨 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脩聝 脨虏 脨潞脨掳脩聡脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脨碌 脩聙脨掳脨路脨麓脨碌脨禄脨赂脩聜脨碌脨禄脩聫.\n脨聵脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脩聝脨鹿脩聜脨碌 脨潞脨掳脨虏脩聥脩聡脨潞脨赂 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脩聜脨戮脩聡脨陆脩聥脩聟 脨赂脨录脨碌脨陆 脨潞脨掳脩聜脨掳脨禄脨戮脨鲁脨掳: \"脨垄脨碌脩聛脩聜\".\n脨聵脨禄脨赂 脨赂脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脩聝脨鹿脩聜脨碌 Regex \'^[.].*\'\n脨驴脩聙脨赂脨录脨碌脩聙脩聥: ^\\..*\n\"test\"\n\"Test\"\n.*secret.*\n.*BACKUP.*\n.*.ini</string>
    <string name="regex_search">脨聼脨戮脨赂脩聛脨潞 脨驴脨戮 脨虏脩聥脩聙脨掳脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫脨录</string>
    <string name="case_sensitive">脨拢脩聡脨赂脩聜脩聥脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聙脨碌脨鲁脨赂脩聛脩聜脩聙</string>
    <string name="stop_search_after_first_match">脨聻脩聛脩聜脨掳脨陆脨戮脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨驴脨戮脨赂脩聛脨潞 脩聛 脨驴脨碌脩聙脨虏脩聥脨录 脩聛脨戮脨虏脨驴脨掳脨麓脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌脨录</string>
    <string name="regex_can_not_be_compiled">脨聺脨碌 脩聝脨麓脨掳脨禄脨戮脩聛脩聦 脩聛脨潞脨戮脨录脨驴脨赂脨禄脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脩聜脩聦 Regex</string>
    <string name="keep_both">脨聻脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨戮脨卤脨掳</string>
    <string name="skip">脨聼脩聙脨戮脨驴脩聝脩聛脩聜脨赂脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="overwrite">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨路脨掳脨驴脨赂脩聛脨掳脩聜脩聦</string>
    <string name="keep_both_all">脨聻脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨戮脨卤脨掳 (脨虏脩聛脨碌)</string>
    <string name="skip_all">脨聼脩聙脨戮脨驴脩聝脩聛脩聜脨赂脩聜脩聦 (脨虏脩聛脨碌)</string>
    <string name="overwrite_all">脨聼脨碌脩聙脨碌脨路脨掳脨驴脨赂脩聛脨掳脩聜脩聦 (脨虏脩聛脨碌)</string>
    <string name="copy_move_conflict_message">\'%1$s\' 脩聝脨露脨碌 脩聛脩聝脩聣脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脩聝脨碌脩聜 脨虏 %2$s</string>
    <string name="additional_contexts_and_projects">脨聰脨戮脨驴脨戮脨禄脨陆脨赂脩聜脨碌脨禄脩聦脨陆脩聥脨碌 脨潞脨戮脨陆脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜脩聥 脨赂 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜脩聥</string>
    <string name="enter_space_seperated_contexts_and_projects_these_will">脨聮脨虏脨碌脨麓脨赂脩聜脨碌 脨潞脨戮脨陆脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜脩聥, 脩聙脨掳脨路脨麓脨碌脨禄脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聥脨碌 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨卤脨碌脨禄脨掳脨录脨赂, 脨赂 +脨驴脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜脩聥. 脨聻脨陆脨赂 脨虏脩聛脨碌脨鲁脨麓脨掳 脨卤脩聝脨麓脩聝脩聜 脨虏脨赂脨麓脨陆脩聥 脨虏 todo.txt 脨麓脨赂脨掳脨禄脨戮脨鲁脨掳脩聟.</string>
    <string name="infinite">脨聭脨碌脩聛脨潞脨戮脨陆脨碌脩聡脨陆脩聥脨鹿</string>
    <string name="browse_by_project">脨聼脩聙脨戮脩聛脨录脨戮脩聜脩聙 脨驴脨戮 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜脨掳脨录</string>
    <string name="browse_by_context">脨聼脩聙脨戮脩聛脨录脨戮脩聜脩聙 脨驴脨戮 脨潞脨戮脨陆脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜脩聝</string>
    <string name="insert_project">脨聮脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨驴脩聙脨戮脨碌脨潞脩聜脩聥</string>
    <string name="insert_context">脨聮脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨潞脨戮脨陆脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜</string>
    <string name="browse_todo">脨聻脨卤脨路脨戮脩聙 脨路脨掳脨麓脨掳脩聡脨赂</string>
    <string name="browse_by_priority">脨聼脩聙脨戮脩聛脨录脨戮脩聜脩聙 脨驴脨戮 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨戮脩聙脨赂脩聜脨碌脩聜脩聝</string>
    <string name="browse_by_due_date">脨聼脩聙脨戮脩聛脨录脨戮脩聜脩聙 脨驴脨戮 脨麓脨掳脩聜脨碌 脨虏脩聥脨驴脨戮脨禄脨陆脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="due_overdue">脨聼脩聙脨戮脩聛脩聙脨戮脩聡脨碌脨陆脨戮</string>
    <string name="due_today">脨隆脩聙脨戮脨潞 脩聛脨麓脨掳脩聡脨赂 脩聛脨碌脨鲁脨戮脨麓脨陆脩聫</string>
    <string name="due_future">脨聮脩聥脨驴脨戮脨禄脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨虏 脨卤脩聝脨麓脩聝脩聣脨碌脨录</string>
    <string name="completed">脨聮脩聥脨驴脨戮脨禄脨陆脨碌脨陆脨戮</string>
    <string name="advanced_filtering">脨聼脩聙脨戮脨麓脨虏脨赂脨陆脩聝脩聜脨掳脩聫 脩聞脨赂脨禄脩聦脩聜脩聙脨掳脩聠脨赂脩聫</string>
    <string name="match_any">脨聸脩聨脨卤脨戮脨碌 脩聛脨戮脨虏脨驴脨掳脨麓脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="match_all">脨聼脨戮脨禄脨陆脨戮脨碌 脩聛脨戮脨虏脨驴脨掳脨麓脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌</string>
    <string name="dynamic_notebook_root_links">脨聰脨赂脨陆脨掳脨录脨赂脩聡脨碌脩聛脨潞脨赂脨鹿 脨驴脨戮脨赂脩聛脨潞 脨潞脨戮脩聙脨陆脩聫 脨卤脨禄脨戮脨潞脨陆脨戮脩聜脨掳</string>
    <string name="search_dynamically_for_notebook_root">脨搂脩聜脨戮脨卤脩聥 脨驴脨碌脩聙脨碌脨鹿脩聜脨赂 脨驴脨戮 脨虏脨赂脨潞脨赂-脩聛脩聛脩聥脨禄脨潞脨掳脨录, 脨陆脨碌脨戮脨卤脩聟脨戮脨麓脨赂脨录脨戮 脨麓脨赂脨陆脨掳脨录脨赂脩聡脨碌脩聛脨潞脨赂 脨赂脩聛脨潞脨掳脩聜脩聦 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄 notebook.zim 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脨戮脨驴脩聙脨碌脨麓脨碌脨禄脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨潞脨戮脩聙脨陆脨碌脨虏脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脨潞脨掳脩聜脨掳脨禄脨戮脨鲁脨掳 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聝脩聣脨碌脨鹿 脨路脨掳脨驴脨赂脩聛脨陆脨戮脨鹿 脨潞脨陆脨赂脨露脨潞脨赂. 脨拢脩聛脩聜脨掳脨陆脨戮脨虏脨赂脩聜脨碌 脩聞脨禄脨掳脨露脨戮脨潞, 脨碌脩聛脨禄脨赂 脨虏脩聥 脨赂脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脩聝脨碌脩聜脨碌 脨陆脨碌脩聛脨潞脨戮脨禄脩聦脨潞脨戮 脩聠脨赂脨录-脨卤脨禄脨戮脨潞脨陆脨戮脩聜脨戮脨虏 脨赂脨禄脨赂 脩聝脩聛脩聜脨掳脨陆脨戮脨虏脨禄脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脨虏 脨驴脩聙脨赂脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨赂 脨潞脨掳脩聜脨掳脨禄脨戮脨鲁 脨卤脨禄脨戮脨潞脨陆脨戮脩聜脨掳 脨陆脨碌 脩聛脨戮脨戮脩聜脨虏脨碌脩聜脩聛脩聜脨虏脩聝脨碌脩聜 脨虏脨掳脩聢脨碌脨录脩聝 脨卤脨禄脨戮脨潞脨陆脨戮脩聜脩聝 zim.</string>
    <string name="share_into_format_prefix_for_text_shared">脨陇脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜/脨聼脩聙脨碌脩聞脨赂脨潞脩聛 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜脨掳, 脨戮脩聜脨驴脩聙脨掳脨虏脨禄脨碌脨陆脨陆脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脨虏 Portal. 脨隆脨戮脨戮脩聜脨虏脨碌脩聜脩聛脩聜脨虏脩聝脨碌脩聜 脨驴脩聙脨掳脨虏脨赂脨禄脨掳脨录 Android SimpleDateFormat. \n\n脨聵脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脩聝脨鹿脩聜脨碌 脨驴脨碌脩聙脨碌脨录脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聝脩聨 \'{{text}}\' (脩聛 脨戮脨麓脨赂脨陆脨掳脩聙脨陆脩聥脨录脨赂 脨潞脨掳脨虏脩聥脩聡脨潞脨掳脨录脨赂) 脨麓脨禄脩聫 脩聙脨掳脨路脨录脨碌脩聣脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨戮脩聜脨驴脩聙脨掳脨虏脨禄脨碌脨陆脨陆脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜脨掳. 脨聲脩聛脨禄脨赂 脨陆脨碌 脩聝脨潞脨掳脨路脨掳脨陆脨戮, 脨戮脩聜脨驴脩聙脨掳脨虏脨禄脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜 脨麓脨戮脨卤脨掳脨虏脨禄脩聫脨碌脩聜脩聛脩聫 脨赂 脩聞脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜 脨赂脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脩聝脨碌脩聜脩聛脩聫 脨虏 脨潞脨掳脩聡脨碌脩聛脩聜脨虏脨碌 脨驴脩聙脨碌脩聞脨赂脨潞脩聛脨掳.</string>
    <string name="share_into_format">脨聼脨戮脨麓脨碌脨禄脨赂脩聜脩聦脩聛脩聫 - 脨陇脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜</string>
    <string name="attachment_folder_name">脨聺脨掳脨路脨虏脨掳脨陆脨赂脨碌 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨赂 脩聛 脨虏脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脨碌脨录</string>
    <string name="attachment_folder_name_desc">脨聼脨戮脨麓脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨掳 脨虏 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聝脩聣脨碌脨鹿 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨碌, 脨鲁脨麓脨碌 脨卤脩聝脨麓脩聝脩聜 脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦脩聛脩聫 脨虏脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫. 脨聲脩聛脨禄脨赂 脨戮脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脨驴脩聝脩聛脩聜脩聥脨录, 脩聜脨戮 脨虏脨禄脨戮脨露脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨卤脩聝脨麓脩聝脩聜 脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脨赂脩聜脩聦脩聛脩聫 脨虏 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聝脩聣脨碌脨鹿 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨碌.</string>
    <string name="auto_format">脨聬脨虏脩聜脨戮脩聞脨戮脩聙脨录脨掳脩聜</string>
    <string name="insert_snippet">脨聮脩聛脩聜脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聜脩聦 脩聞脩聙脨掳脨鲁脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜</string>
    <string name="snippet_directory">脨聰脨赂脩聙脨碌脨潞脩聜脨戮脩聙脨赂脩聫 脩聛 脩聞脩聙脨掳脨鲁脨录脨碌脨陆脩聜脨掳脨录脨赂 / 脩聢脨掳脨卤脨禄脨戮脨陆脨掳脨录脨赂</string>
    <string name="error_could_not_open_file">脨聻脩聢脨赂脨卤脨潞脨掳: 脨聺脨碌 脩聝脨麓脨掳脨禄脨戮脩聛脩聦 脨戮脩聜脨潞脩聙脩聥脩聜脩聦 脩聞脨掳脨鹿脨禄.</string>
    <string name="document_error_clip">脨聼脩聙脨戮脨赂脨路脨戮脩聢脨禄脨掳 脨戮脩聢脨赂脨卤脨潞脨掳: 脩聜脨碌脨潞脩聛脩聜 脩聛脨潞脨戮脨驴脨赂脩聙脨戮脨虏脨掳脨陆 脨虏 脨卤脩聝脩聞脨碌脩聙 脨戮脨卤脨录脨碌脨陆脨掳.</string>
    <string name="wont_save_min_length">脨陇脨掳脨鹿脨禄脩聥 脩聛脨戮脨麓脨碌脩聙脨露脨掳脩聣脨赂脨碌 脨录脨碌脨陆脨碌脨碌 %d 脩聛脨赂脨录脨虏脨戮脨禄脨戮脨虏 脨陆脨碌 脩聛脨戮脩聟脩聙脨掳脨陆脩聫脩聨脩聜脩聛脩聫 脨掳脨虏脩聜脨戮脨录脨掳脩聜脨赂脩聡脨碌脩聛脨潞脨赂 脨虏脨戮 脨赂脨路脨卤脨碌脨露脨掳脨陆脨赂脨碌 脩聛脨禄脩聝脩聡脨掳脨鹿脨陆脨戮脨鲁脨戮 脩聝脨麓脨掳脨禄脨碌脨陆脨赂脩聫 脨麓脨掳脨陆脨陆脩聥脩聟.</string>
    <string name="advanced_filtering_help"><![CDATA[<small><a href="https://github.com/mattg101/portal/discussions">脨聽脨掳脩聛脩聢脨赂脩聙脨碌脨陆脨陆脩聥脨鹿 脩聛脨赂脨陆脩聜脨掳脨潞脩聛脨赂脩聛 脩聞脨赂脨禄脩聦脩聜脩聙脨掳脩聠脨赂脨赂</a></small>]]></string>
    <string name="filter">脨陇脨赂脨禄脩聦脩聜脩聙</string>
    <string name="text_case">脨聽脨碌脨鲁脨赂脩聛脩聜脩聙</string>
    <string name="use_tab_to_indent">脨隆脨麓脨虏脨赂脨陆脩聝脩聜脩聦 脩聛脩聜脩聙脨戮脨潞脨赂 脨虏脨驴脩聙脨掳脨虏脨戮 脨赂脩聛脨驴脨戮脨禄脩聦脨路脩聝脩聫 脨潞脨禄脨掳脨虏脨赂脩聢脩聝 TAB</string>
    <string name="folder_local">脨聸脨戮脨潞脨掳脨禄脩聦脨陆脨掳脩聫 脨驴脨掳脨驴脨潞脨掳</string>
</resources>
