<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
Maintained 2017-2025 by Gregor Santner <gsantner AT mailbox DOT org>

To the extent possible under law, the person who associated CC0 with
this file has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights
to the public domain.

You should have received a copy of the CC0 legalcode along with this
work. If not, see <https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/>.
-->
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="settings">脦隆脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聜</string>
    <string name="light">脦聭脦陆脦驴脦鹿脦潞脧聞脧聦</string>
    <string name="dark">脦拢脦潞脦驴脧聞脦碌脦鹿脦陆脧聦</string>
    <string name="delete">脦聰脦鹿脦卤脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦庐</string>
    <string name="appearance">脦聲脦录脧聠脦卢脦陆脦鹿脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="rename">脦聹脦碌脧聞脦驴脦陆脦驴脦录脦卤脧聝脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="confirm_delete">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦虏脦碌脦虏脦卤脦炉脧聣脧聝脦路 脦聰脦鹿脦卤脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="do_you_really_want_to_delete_this_witharg">脦聵脦颅脦禄脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聙脧聛脦卤脦鲁脦录脦卤脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卢 脦陆脦卤 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聢脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴 %s?</string>
    <string name="confirm_overwrite">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦虏脦碌脦虏脦卤脦炉脧聣脧聝脦路 脦聭脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="file_already_exists_overwerite">脦陇脦驴 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脧聟脧聙脦卢脧聛脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脦庐脦麓脦路, 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路;</string>
    <string name="browse_filesystem">脦聽脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦庐脦鲁脦路脧聝脦路 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脧聝脧聧脧聝脧聞脦路脦录脦卤 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="title">脦陇脦炉脧聞脦禄脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="empty_directory">脦職脦碌脦陆脧聦脧聜 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="enter_name_of_folder">脦聲脦鹿脧聝脦卢脦鲁脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴 脧聦脦陆脦驴脦录脦卤 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脧聠脦卤脦潞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聟 脧聝脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="create_folder">脦聰脦路脦录脦鹿脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤 脦娄脦卤脦潞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="create_new_document">脦聰脦路脦录脦鹿脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤 脦陆脦颅脦驴脧聟 脦碌脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="move">脦聹脦碌脧聞脦卤脦潞脦炉脦陆脦路脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="info">脦聽脦禄脦路脧聛脦驴脧聠脦驴脧聛脦炉脦碌脧聜</string>
    <string name="file_folder_already_exists_please_use_a_different_name">脦陇脦驴 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴/脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴脧聜 脧聟脧聙脦卢脧聛脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脦庐脦麓脦路! 脦聽脦卤脧聛脦卤脦潞脦卤脦禄脦驴脧聧脦录脦碌 脧聡脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脦颅脦陆脦卤 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脧聠脦驴脧聛脦碌脧聞脦鹿脦潞脧聦 脧聦脦陆脦驴脦录脦卤</string>
    <string name="import_from_device">脦聲脦鹿脧聝脦卤脦鲁脧聣脦鲁脦庐 脦卤脧聙脧聦 脧聞脦路 脧聝脧聟脧聝脦潞脦碌脧聟脦庐</string>
    <string name="import_">脦聲脦鹿脧聝脦卤脦鲁脧聣脦鲁脦庐</string>
    <string name="append_to_witharg">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脦卢脧聛脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脧聝脦碌 %s</string>
    <string name="select_folder">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦庐 脧聠脦卤脦潞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="edit">脦聲脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="search_documents">脦聭脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脦碌脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦驴脧聟(脧聣脦陆)</string>
    <string name="share_to_arrow" tools:ignore="TypographyEllipsis">脦職脦驴脦鹿脦陆脦庐 脧聡脧聛脦庐脧聝脦路 脧聝脦碌&#8230;</string>
    <string name="share">脦職脦驴脦鹿脦陆脦驴脧聙脦驴脦炉脦路脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="search">脦聭脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="display_converted_markup">脦聲脦录脧聠脦卢脦陆脦鹿脧聝脦路 markup 脧聙脦驴脧聟 脦颅脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脦录脦碌脧聞脦卤脧聞脧聛脦卤脧聙脦碌脦炉</string>
    <string name="editor">脦聲脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脧聞脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="folders">脦娄脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴脦鹿</string>
    <string name="files">脦聭脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="document">脦聢脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦驴</string>
    <string name="documents">脦聢脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦卤</string>
    <string name="html_as_plaintext">HTML (脧聣脧聜 脦卤脧聙脦禄脧聦 脦潞脦碌脦炉脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴)</string>
    <string name="document_editor_font">脦聯脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦卤脧聞脦驴脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦卢 脦聲脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脧聞脦庐 脦聲脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="theme">脦聵脦颅脦录脦卤</string>
    <string name="open_existing_files_in_view_mode">脦聠脦陆脦驴脦鹿脦鲁脦录脦卤 脧聟脧聙脦卤脧聛脧聡脧聦脦陆脧聞脧聣脦陆 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脧聣脦陆 脧聝脦碌 脦禄脦碌脦鹿脧聞脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦虏脦驴脦禄脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="about">脦拢脧聡脦碌脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卢</string>
    <string name="plaintext">脦聭脧聙脦禄脧聦 脦職脦碌脦炉脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴</string>
    <string name="file">脦聭脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴</string>
    <string name="image">脦聲脦鹿脦潞脧聦脦陆脦卤</string>
    <string name="font_size">脦聹脦颅脦鲁脦碌脦赂脦驴脧聜 脦聯脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦卤脧聞脦驴脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦卢脧聜</string>
    <string name="render_rtl_language">脦搂脧聛脦庐脧聝脦路 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦鲁脦禄脧聨脧聝脧聝脦碌脧聜 脦录脦碌 脧聠脦驴脧聛脦卢 脦麓脦碌脦戮脦鹿脦卢-脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聜-脦卤脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦碌脧聛脦卢</string>
    <string name="error_cannot_create_notebook_dir__appspecific">脦拢脧聠脦卢脦禄脦录脦卤: 脦聰脦碌脦陆 脦碌脦炉脦陆脦卤脦鹿 脦麓脧聟脦陆脦卤脧聞脦庐 脦路 脦麓脦路脦录脦鹿脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卤脦禄脧聦脦鲁脦驴脧聟 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦赂脦庐脦潞脦碌脧聟脧聝脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="last_modified_witharg">脦陇脦碌脦禄脦碌脧聟脧聞脦卤脦炉脦卤 脧聞脧聛脦驴脧聙脦驴脧聙脦驴脦炉脦路脧聝脦路: %s</string>
    <string name="last_modified">脦陇脦碌脦禄脦碌脧聟脧聞脦卤脦炉脦卤 脧聞脧聛脦驴脧聙脦驴脧聙脦驴脦炉脦路脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="select_this_folder">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦颅脦戮脧聞脦碌 脦卤脧聟脧聞脧聦脦陆 脧聞脦驴脦陆 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴</string>
    <string name="select">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦庐</string>
    <string name="create">脦聰脦路脦录脦鹿脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="select_entries">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦颅脦戮脧聞脦碌 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卤脧聡脧聣脧聛脦庐脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聜</string>
    <string name="one_item_selected">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦颅脧聡脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌 脦颅脦陆脦卤 脧聝脧聞脦驴脦鹿脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴</string>
    <string name="items_selected_witharg" tools:ignore="PluralsCandidate">%d 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦碌脦鲁脦录脦颅脦陆脦卤 脧聝脧聞脦驴脦鹿脧聡脦碌脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="hide_statusbar_at_this_view">脦聭脧聙脧聦脦潞脧聛脧聟脧聢脦路 脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦庐脧聜 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路脧聜 脧聝脦碌 脦卤脧聟脧聞脦庐脦陆 脧聞脦路脦陆 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦虏脦驴脦禄脦庐</string>
    <string name="hide_statusbar">脦聭脧聙脧聦脦潞脧聛脧聟脧聢脦路 脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦庐脧聜 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="name">脦聦脦陆脦驴脦录脦卤</string>
    <string name="url_or_path">URL / 脦聰脦鹿脦卤脦麓脧聛脦驴脦录脦庐</string>
    <string name="insert_image">脦聲脦鹿脧聝脦卤脦鲁脧聣脦鲁脦庐 脦碌脦鹿脦潞脧聦脦陆脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="contributors">脦拢脧聟脦陆脧聞脦碌脦禄脦碌脧聝脧聞脦颅脧聜</string>
    <string name="save_location">脦聭脧聙脦驴脦赂脦庐脦潞脦碌脧聟脧聝脦路 脧聞脦驴脧聙脦驴脦赂脦碌脧聝脦炉脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="saved_location_to">脦聭脧聙脦驴脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌脧聧脧聞脦路脦潞脦碌 脧聝脦碌 %s</string>
    <string name="select_storage_folder">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦庐 脧聠脦卤脦潞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聟 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦赂脦庐脦潞脦碌脧聟脧聝脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="licenses">脦聠脦麓脦碌脦鹿脦碌脧聜</string>
    <string name="changelog">脦聭脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脦聭脦禄脦禄脦卤脦鲁脧聨脦陆</string>
    <string name="more_info">脦聽脦碌脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聝脧聦脧聞脦碌脧聛脦碌脧聜 脧聙脦禄脦路脧聛脦驴脧聠脦驴脧聛脦炉脦碌脧聜</string>
    <string name="show_license_of_the_app">脦聲脦录脧聠脦卢脦陆脦鹿脧聝脦路 脦卢脦麓脦碌脦鹿脦卤脧聜 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="show_third_party_licenses">脦聲脦录脧聠脦卢脦陆脦鹿脧聝脦路 脦卤脦麓脦碌脦鹿脧聨脦陆 脧聞脧聛脦炉脧聞脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="language_change_restart_description">脦聭脦禄脦禄脦卤脦鲁脦庐 脦鲁脦禄脧聨脧聝脧聝脦卤脧聜 脦卤脧聟脧聞脦庐脧聜 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜. 脦聲脧聙脦卤脦陆脦碌脦潞脦潞脦炉脦陆脦路脧聝脦路 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脧聞脦碌脦赂脦驴脧聧脦陆 脧聝脦碌 脦鹿脧聝脧聡脧聧 脦驴脦鹿 脦卤脦禄脦禄脦卤脦鲁脦颅脧聜</string>
    <string name="language">脦聯脦禄脧聨脧聝脧聝脦卤</string>
    <string name="storage_permission_required">脦聠脦麓脦碌脦鹿脦卤 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦赂脦庐脦潞脦碌脧聟脧聝脦路脧聜 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脧聣脦陆 脦碌脦炉脦陆脦卤脦鹿 脦卤脧聙脦卤脧聛脦卤脦炉脧聞脦路脧聞脦路</string>
    <string name="open_with">脦聠脦陆脦驴脦鹿脦鲁脦录脦卤 脦录脦碌</string>
    <string name="sort_by">脦陇脦卤脦戮脦鹿脦陆脧聦脦录脦路脧聝脦路 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢</string>
    <string name="date">脦聴脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="deleteme____1">脦聦脦陆脦驴脦录脦卤</string>
    <string name="size">脦聹脦颅脦鲁脦碌脦赂脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="reverse_order">脦聭脦陆脧聞脦炉脧聝脧聞脧聛脦驴脧聠脦路 脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦卢</string>
    <string name="contribute">脦拢脧聟脦陆脦碌脦鹿脧聝脧聠脦颅脧聛脦碌脧聞脦碌</string>
    <string name="project_page">脦拢脦碌脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤 脦颅脧聛脦鲁脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="press_back_again_to_exit">脦聽脦卤脧聞脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脦戮脦卤脦陆脦卢 \'脦聽脦炉脧聝脧聣\' 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦颅脦戮脦驴脦麓脦驴</string>
    <string name="exit">脦聢脦戮脦驴脦麓脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="undo">脦聭脦陆脦卤脦炉脧聛脦碌脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="redo">脦聲脧聙脦卤脦陆脦卢脦禄脦路脧聢脦路</string>
    <string name="more">脦聽脦碌脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聝脧聦脧聞脦碌脧聛脦卤</string>
    <string name="notebook">脦拢脦路脦录脦碌脦鹿脧聣脦录脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聛脦鹿脦驴</string>
    <string name="help">脦聮脦驴脦庐脦赂脦碌脦鹿脦卤</string>
    <string name="todo_list">脦聸脦炉脧聝脧聞脦卤 脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聜 脧聟脦禄脦驴脧聙脦驴脦炉脦路脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="task">脦聲脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="context">脦聽脦禄脦卤脦炉脧聝脦鹿脦驴</string>
    <string name="list">脦聸脦炉脧聝脧聞脦卤</string>
    <string name="priority">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聞脦碌脧聛脦卤脦鹿脧聦脧聞脦路脧聞脦卤</string>
    <string name="history">脦聶脧聝脧聞脦驴脧聛脦鹿脦潞脧聦</string>
    <string name="sync">脦拢脧聟脦鲁脧聡脧聛脦驴脦陆脦鹿脧聝脦录脧聦脧聜</string>
    <string name="search_or_custom">脦聭脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 / 脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脧聝脦录脦颅脦陆脦路</string>
    <string name="save">脦聭脧聙脦驴脦赂脦庐脦潞脦碌脧聟脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="update">脦聲脦陆脦路脦录脦颅脧聛脧聣脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="clear">脦聲脦潞脦潞脦卤脦赂脦卢脧聛脦鹿脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="due_date">脦聴脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤 脦禄脦庐脦戮脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="current_date">脦陇脧聛脦颅脧聡脦驴脧聟脧聝脦卤 脦路脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="archive">脦聭脧聛脧聡脦碌脦鹿脦驴脦赂脦颅脧聞脦路脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="add_task">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脦赂脦庐脦潞脦路 脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦炉脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="add_x_witharg">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脦赂脦庐脦潞脦路 %s</string>
    <string name="document_to_be_loaded_and_saved_as_witharg">脦聢脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦驴 脧聙脦驴脧聟 脦赂脦卤 脧聠脦驴脧聛脧聞脧聣脦赂脦碌脦炉 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦赂脦卤 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌脧聟脧聞脦碌脦炉 脧聣脧聜 \"%s\"</string>
    <string name="refresh">脦聭脦陆脦卤脦陆脦颅脧聣脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="create_shortcut">脦聰脦路脦录脦鹿脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤 脧聝脧聟脦陆脧聞脧聦脦录脦碌脧聟脧聝脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="tried_to_create_shortcut_for_this_notice">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脧聙脦卢脦赂脦路脧聝脦碌 脦陆脦卤 脦麓脦路脦录脦鹿脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦庐脧聝脦碌脦鹿 脦录脦鹿脦卤 脧聝脧聟脦陆脧聞脧聦脦录脦碌脧聟脧聝脦路 脧聝脧聞脦路脦陆 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦鹿脦潞脦庐 脦驴脦赂脧聦脦陆脦路. 脦拢脦路脦录脦碌脦鹿脧聨脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聦脧聞脦鹿 脦驴脧聛脦鹿脧聝脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脦鹿 脦碌脦潞脦潞脦鹿脦陆脦路脧聞脦颅脧聜 脦碌脦陆脦麓脦颅脧聡脦碌脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脦陆脦卤 脦录脦路脦陆 脧聞脦驴 脧聟脧聙脦驴脧聝脧聞脦路脧聛脦炉脦戮脦驴脧聟脦陆.</string>
    <string name="file_not_in_save_path_do_import_notice__appspecific">脦陇脦驴 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦碌脦鲁脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脦虏脧聛脦炉脧聝脦潞脦碌脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脧聝脧聞脦驴脦陆 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦驴 脧聝脦路脦录脦碌脦鹿脧聣脦录脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聛脦鹿脧聣脦陆 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜. 脦聵脦颅脦禄脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦陆脦卤 脧聞脦驴 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聢脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聝脧聞脦驴脦陆 脧聞脧聛脦颅脧聡脦驴脦陆脧聞脦卤 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴? 脦聭脧聟脧聞脧聦 脦赂脦卤 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卤脧聝脧聞脦庐脧聝脦碌脦鹿 脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦驴脦麓脦庐脧聙脦驴脧聞脦碌 脧聟脧聙脦卢脧聛脧聡脦驴脦陆 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脦录脦碌 脧聞脦驴 脦炉脦麓脦鹿脦驴 脧聦脦陆脦驴脦录脦卤.</string>
    <string name="file_not_in_current_folder_do_copy__appspecific">脦陇脦驴 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脦虏脧聛脦炉脧聝脦潞脦碌脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脧聝脧聞脦驴脦陆 脧聞脧聛脦颅脧聡脦驴脦陆脧聞脦卤 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴. 脦聵脦颅脦禄脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦陆脦卤 脧聞脦驴 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聢脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聝脧聞脦驴脦陆 脧聞脧聛脦颅脧聡脦驴脦陆脧聞脦卤 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴? 脦聭脧聟脧聞脧聦 脦赂脦卤 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卤脧聝脧聞脦庐脧聝脦碌脦鹿 脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦驴脦麓脦庐脧聙脦驴脧聞脦碌 脧聟脧聙脦卢脧聛脧聡脦驴脦陆 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脦录脦碌 脧聞脦驴 脦炉脦麓脦鹿脦驴 脧聦脦陆脦驴脦录脦卤.</string>
    <string name="files_and_folders">脦聭脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦卤 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴脦鹿</string>
    <string name="document_browser">脦聽脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦路脦鲁脦路脧聞脦庐脧聜 脦碌脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="file_browser">脦聽脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦路脦鲁脦路脧聞脦庐脧聜 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="set_due_date">脦聼脧聛脦鹿脧聝脦录脧聦脧聜 脦路脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤脧聜 脦禄脦庐脦戮脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="insert_replace_date">脦聲脦鹿脧聝脦卤脦鲁脧聣脦鲁脦庐 脦路脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="create_note" needed="false">脦聰脦路脦录脦鹿脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤 脦拢脦路脦录脦碌脦炉脧聣脧聝脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="special_documents" needed="false">脦聲脦鹿脦麓脦鹿脦潞脦卢 脦颅脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦卤</string>
    <string name="keep_screen_on" needed="false">脦聰脦鹿脦卤脧聞脦庐脧聛脦路脧聝脦路 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦驴脦赂脧聦脦陆脦路脧聜 脦碌脦陆脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="disallow_screenshots">脦聭脧聙脦卤脦鲁脧聦脧聛脦碌脧聟脧聝脦路 脧聝脧聞脦鹿脦鲁脦录脦鹿脧聦脧聞脧聟脧聙脧聣脦陆 脦驴脦赂脧聦脦陆脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="back_to_previous_folder" needed="false">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脧聝脧聞脧聛脦驴脧聠脦庐 脧聝脧聞脦驴脦陆 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦路脦鲁脦驴脧聧脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴</string>
    <string name="app_settings" needed="false">脦隆脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聜 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="editor_settings" needed="false">脦隆脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聜 脦聲脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脧聞脦庐</string>
    <string name="remember_last_folder_location_on_startup" needed="false">脦聭脧聙脦驴脦录脦陆脦路脦录脧聦脦陆脦碌脧聟脧聝脦路 脧聞脦路脧聜 脧聞脦碌脦禄脦碌脧聟脧聞脦卤脦炉脦卤脧聜 脧聞脦驴脧聙脦驴脦赂脦碌脧聝脦炉脦卤脧聜 脧聠脦卤脦潞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聟 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脦潞脦潞脦炉脦陆脦路脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="number_of_files_witharg" needed="false">脦聭脧聛脦鹿脦赂脦录脧聦脧聜 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脧聣脦陆: %d</string>
    <string name="app_wide">脦聲脧聧脧聛脦驴脧聜 脦聲脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="main_view">脦職脧聧脧聛脦鹿脦卤 脦聽脧聛脦驴脦虏脦驴脦禄脦庐</string>
    <string name="overall_theme_used_in_app">脦陇脦驴 脦鲁脦碌脦陆脦鹿脦潞脧聦 脦赂脦颅脦录脦卤 脧聙脦驴脧聟 脧聡脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦碌脦炉脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脧聝脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐</string>
    <string name="remember_last_directory">脦聭脧聙脦驴脦录脦陆脦路脦录脧聦脦陆脦碌脧聟脧聝脦路 脧聞脦碌脦禄脦碌脧聟脧聞脦卤脦炉脦驴脧聟 脧聠脦卤脦潞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="syntax_highlighting">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脧聝脦庐脦录脦卤脦陆脧聝脦路 脧聝脧聧脦陆脧聞脦卤脦戮脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="highlighting_delay">脦職脦卤脦赂脧聟脧聝脧聞脦颅脧聛脦路脧聝脦路 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脧聝脦庐脦录脦卤脦陆脧聝脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="highlighting_delay_lower_value_more_battery_drain_description__appspecific">脦職脦卤脦赂脧聟脧聝脧聞脦颅脧聛脦路脧聝脦路 脧聝脦碌 脧聡脦鹿脦禄脦鹿脦驴脧聝脧聞脦卢 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦麓脦碌脧聟脧聞脦碌脧聛脦驴脦禄脦颅脧聙脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦卤脦陆脦卤脦陆脦颅脧聣脧聝脦路 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脧聝脦庐脦录脦卤脦陆脧聝脦路脧聜. 脦聹脦鹿脦卤 脧聡脦卤脦录脦路脦禄脧聦脧聞脦碌脧聛脦路 脧聞脦鹿脦录脦庐 脦赂脦卤 脦戮脦碌脦潞脦鹿脦陆脦庐脧聝脦碌脦鹿 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脧聝脦庐脦录脦卤脦陆脧聝脦路 脦陆脧聣脧聛脦炉脧聞脦碌脧聛脦卤, 脦卤脦禄脦禄脦卢 脦赂脦卤 脦碌脦戮脦卤脦陆脧聞脦禄脦庐脧聝脦碌脦鹿 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦录脧聙脦卤脧聞脦卤脧聛脦炉脦卤 脧聝脦卤脧聜 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦碌脦陆脦麓脦颅脧聡脦碌脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脦陆脦卤 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦虏脧聛脦卤脦麓脧聧脦陆脦碌脦鹿 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐 脧聝脦碌 脧聙脦卤脦禄脦卤脦鹿脧聦脧聞脦碌脧聛脦碌脧聜 脧聝脧聟脧聝脦潞脦碌脧聟脦颅脧聜.</string>
    <string name="highlighting_enabled_or_not__appspecific">脦聲脦禄脦颅脦鲁脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脦卤脦陆 脧聞脦驴 脦碌脦鹿脧聝脦卤脧聡脦赂脦颅脦陆 脦潞脦碌脦炉脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴 脧聙脧聛脦颅脧聙脦碌脦鹿 脦陆脦卤 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脧聝脦路脦录脦卤脦陆脦赂脦碌脦炉 脦庐 脧聦脧聡脦鹿</string>
    <string name="control_font_size_in_editor">脦聢脦禄脦碌脦鲁脧聡脦驴脧聜 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦录脦碌脦鲁脦颅脦赂脦驴脧聟脧聜 脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦卤脧聞脦驴脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦卢脧聜 脧聙脦驴脧聟 脧聡脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦碌脦炉脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脧聝脧聞脦驴脦陆 脦碌脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脧聞脦庐</string>
    <string name="textactions_show_useful_actions_description__appspecific">脦聲脦录脧聠脦卢脦陆脦鹿脧聝脦路 脦录脦鹿脦卤脧聜 脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦庐脧聜 脦录脦碌 脦碌脧聧脧聡脧聛脦路脧聝脧聞脦卤 脦潞脦驴脧聟脦录脧聙脦鹿脦卢 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脦潞脦卢脧聞脧聣 脦录脦颅脧聛脦驴脧聜. 脦聭脧聟脧聞脦颅脧聜 脦驴脦鹿 脦碌脦陆脦颅脧聛脦鲁脦碌脦鹿脦碌脧聜 脦潞脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟 脧聞脧聛脦驴脧聙脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦驴脧聧脦陆 脧聞脦驴 脦潞脦碌脦炉脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴 脦庐 脧聞脧聛脦颅脧聡脦驴脧聟脦陆 脦录脦鹿脦卤 脦碌脦陆脦颅脧聛脦鲁脦碌脦鹿脦卤 脦虏脦卤脧聝脦鹿脧聝脦录脦颅脦陆脦路 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脦潞脦碌脦炉脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴.</string>
    <string name="load_last_opened_folder_at_startup">脦娄脧聦脧聛脧聞脧聣脧聝脦路 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脧聞脦碌脦禄脦碌脧聟脧聞脦卤脦炉脦驴脧聟 脦卤脦陆脦驴脦鹿脦鲁脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟 脧聠脦卤脦潞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聟 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脦潞脦潞脦炉脦陆脦路脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="format">脦聹脦驴脧聛脧聠脦庐</string>
    <string name="contexts">脦拢脧聟脦鲁脦潞脦碌脦炉脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴</string>
    <string name="project">脦聢脧聛脦鲁脦驴</string>
    <string name="projects">脦聢脧聛脦鲁脦卤</string>
    <string name="none">脦職脦卤脦陆脦颅脦陆脦卤</string>
    <string name="other">脦聠脦禄脦禄脦驴</string>
    <string name="empty_file">脦職脦碌脦陆脧聦 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴</string>
    <string name="break_page_pdf_print">脦拢脦碌脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脦潞脦驴脧聙脦庐脧聜 (PDF/脦聲脦潞脧聞脧聧脧聙脧聣脧聝脦路)</string>
    <string name="underline">脦聹脦碌 脧聟脧聙脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卢脦录脦录脦鹿脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="underline_hex_color_wether_or_not_to_description__appspecific">脦聭脦陆 脦赂脦卤 脧聟脧聙脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦碌脦炉 脦驴 脦麓脦碌脦潞脦卤脦碌脦戮脦卤脦麓脦鹿脦潞脧聦脧聜 脦潞脧聣脦麓脦鹿脦潞脧聦脧聜 脧聡脧聛脧聨脦录脦卤脧聞脦驴脧聜 脧聝脧聧脦录脧聠脧聣脦陆脦卤 脦录脦碌 脧聞脦驴 脧聡脧聛脧聨脦录脦卤</string>
    <string name="underline_hex_color_codes">脦楼脧聙脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卢脦录脦录脦鹿脧聝脦路 脦聰脦碌脦潞脦卤脦碌脦戮脦卤脦麓脦鹿脦潞脦驴脧聧脧聜 脦職脧聣脦麓脦鹿脦潞脦驴脧聧脧聜 脦搂脧聛脧聣脦录脦卢脧聞脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="insert_current_date_when_starting_new_task">脦聲脦鹿脧聝脦卢脦鲁脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦路脦陆 脧聞脧聛脦颅脧聡脦驴脧聟脧聝脦卤 脦路脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦颅脦陆脦卤脧聛脦戮脦路 脦录脦鹿脦卤脧聜 脦陆脦颅脦卤脧聜 脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦炉脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="tasks_with_todays_date">脦聲脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦炉脦碌脧聜 脦录脦碌 脧聞脦路 脧聝脦路脦录脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦陆脦庐 脦路脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="append_contexts_and_projects">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脦卢脧聛脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脧聝脧聟脦鲁脦潞脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脧聣脦陆 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦颅脧聛脦鲁脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="append_contexts_and_projects_on_end_of_task">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脦卢脧聛脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脧聝脧聟脦鲁脦潞脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脧聣脦陆 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦颅脧聛脦鲁脧聣脦陆 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脧聞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聜 脦录脦鹿脦卤脧聜 脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦炉脦卤脧聜 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢 脧聞脦路 脧聡脧聛脦庐脧聝脦路 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脦禄脦禄脦路脦禄脦路脧聜 脦碌脦陆脦颅脧聛脦鲁脦碌脦鹿脦卤脧聜 脦潞脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="rtl_rendering">脦聰脦碌脦戮脦鹿脦卢-脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聜-脦卤脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦碌脧聛脦庐 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦虏脦驴脦禄脦庐</string>
    <string name="highlight_line_ending">脦楼脧聙脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卢脦录脦录脦鹿脧聝脦路 脧聞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聟脧聜 脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="highlight_line_ending_if_two_or_more_spaces">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脧聝脦庐脦录脦卤脦陆脧聝脦路 脦潞脦碌脦陆脧聨脦陆 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脧聞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聜 脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脧聨脦陆 脧聙脦驴脧聟 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦颅脧聡脦驴脧聟脦陆 脦麓脧聧脦驴 脦庐 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聝脧聦脧聞脦碌脧聛脦卤 脦潞脦碌脦陆脦卢</string>
    <string name="use_monospace_for_code">脦搂脧聛脦庐脧聝脦路 脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦卤脧聞脦驴脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦卢脧聜 脧聝脧聞脦卤脦赂脦碌脧聛脦驴脧聧 脧聙脦禄脦卢脧聞脦驴脧聟脧聜 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦潞脧聨脦麓脦鹿脦潞脦卤</string>
    <string name="disable_code_block_highlight">脦聭脧聙脦碌脦陆脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦驴脧聙脦驴脦炉脦路脧聝脦路 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脧聝脦庐脦录脦卤脦陆脧聝脦路脧聜 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦录脧聙脦禄脦驴脦潞 脦潞脧聨脦麓脦鹿脦潞脦卤</string>
    <string name="auto_renumber_ordered_list">脦聭脧聟脧聞脧聦脦录脦卤脧聞脦路 脦碌脧聙脦卤脦陆脦卤脧聛脦炉脦赂脦录脦路脧聝脦路 脧聞脦卤脦戮脦鹿脦陆脦驴脦录脦路脦录脦颅脦陆脧聣脦陆 脦禄脦鹿脧聝脧聞脧聨脦陆</string>
    <string name="auto_renumber_ordered_list_slowdown">脦聭脧聟脧聞脦庐 脦路 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦庐 脦录脧聙脦驴脧聛脦碌脦炉 脦陆脦卤 脦碌脧聙脦路脧聛脦碌脦卢脧聝脦碌脦鹿 脧聞脦鹿脧聜 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦麓脧聦脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聜 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜.</string>
    <string name="use_different_fonttype_slow_down">脦職脦卢脦陆脧聞脦碌 脧聡脧聛脦庐脧聝脦路 脦碌脦陆脧聦脧聜 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脧聠脦驴脧聛脦碌脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦驴脧聧 脧聞脧聧脧聙脦驴脧聟 脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦卤脧聞脦驴脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦卢脧聜. 脦聴 脦卤脦禄脦禄脦卤脦鲁脦庐 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦碌脧聙脦路脧聛脦碌脦卢脦露脦碌脦鹿 脦麓脧聟脦陆脦卤脦录脦鹿脦潞脦卢 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦卤脧聙脧聦脦麓脦驴脧聝脦路 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜.</string>
    <string name="general">脦聯脦碌脦陆脦鹿脦潞脦卢</string>
    <string name="resources">脦聽脧聦脧聛脦驴脦鹿</string>
    <string name="space_between_lines_in_percent">脦聰脦鹿脦卢脧聝脧聞脦路脦录脦卤 脦录脦碌脧聞脦卤脦戮脧聧 脧聞脧聣脦陆 脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脧聨脦陆 脧聝脦碌 脧聙脦驴脧聝脦驴脧聝脧聞脧聦</string>
    <string name="line_spacing">脦聭脧聙脧聦脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路 脦聯脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脧聨脦陆</string>
    <string name="archive_does_move_done_tasks">脦聹脦碌脧聞脦卤脦潞脦炉脦陆脦路脧聝脦路 脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦鹿脧聨脦陆 脧聝脦碌 脦潞脦卤脦赂脦驴脧聛脦鹿脧聝脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脧聝脧聞脦驴脦陆 脦炉脦麓脦鹿脦驴 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴</string>
    <string name="sort_tasks_by_selected_order">脦陇脦卤脦戮脦鹿脦陆脧聦脦录脦路脧聝脦路 脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦鹿脧聨脦陆 脦录脦碌 脦虏脦卢脧聝脦路 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦碌脦鲁脦录脦颅脦陆脦路 脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦卢</string>
    <string name="special_key">脦聲脦鹿脦麓脦鹿脦潞脧聦 脧聙脦禄脦庐脦潞脧聞脧聛脦驴</string>
    <string name="asciidoc_special_key">脦聽脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦碌脧聡脧聦脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴 AsciiDoc</string>
    <string name="key_page_up">脦拢脦碌脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤 脦聲脧聙脦卢脦陆脧聣 (Page Up)</string>
    <string name="key_page_down">脦拢脦碌脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤 脦職脦卢脧聞脧聣 (Page Down)</string>
    <string name="key_pos_1">脦聢脦陆脦卤脧聛脦戮脦路 脦聯脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦庐脧聜 (Pos Home)</string>
    <string name="key_pos_end">脦陇脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聜 脦聯脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦庐脧聜 (Pos 脦陇脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聜)</string>
    <string name="key_pos_1_document">脦聢脦陆脦卤脧聛脦戮脦路 脦聲脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="key_pos_end_document">脦陇脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聜 脦聲脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="key_ctrl_a">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦庐 脧聦脦禄脧聣脦陆 (Ctrl+A)</string>
    <string name="key_tab">脦拢脧聞脦路脦禄脦驴脦赂脦颅脧聞脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="zero_width_space">脦搂脧聨脧聛脦驴脧聜 脦录脦路脦麓脦碌脦陆脦鹿脦潞脦驴脧聧 脧聙脦禄脦卢脧聞脦驴脧聟脧聜</string>
    <string name="start_on_bottom">脦聢脦陆脦卤脧聛脦戮脦路 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脦潞脦卢脧聞脧聣 脦录脦颅脧聛脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="start_on_bottom_when_loading_document">脦聹脦碌脧聞脦卢 脧聞脦路 脧聠脧聦脧聛脧聞脧聣脧聝脦路 脦碌脦陆脧聦脧聜 脦碌脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦驴脧聟, 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦麓脧聛脦驴脦录脦颅脦卤 脦赂脦颅脧聝脦路脧聜 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脧聞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聜 脧聞脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="unordered_list_character">脦搂脦卤脧聛脦卤脦潞脧聞脦庐脧聛脦卤脧聜 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦录脦路 脧聞脦卤脦戮脦鹿脦陆脦驴脦录脦路脦录脦颅脦陆脦路 脦禄脦炉脧聝脧聞脦卤</string>
    <string name="character_to_start_items_of_unordered_list_with">脦聽脦驴脦鹿脦驴脧聜 脧聡脦卤脧聛脦卤脦潞脧聞脦庐脧聛脦卤脧聜 脦陆脦卤 脧聡脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦庐脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脧聟脧聙脦驴脦麓脦碌脦炉脦戮脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦卤脧聞脦卤脦戮脦鹿脦陆脧聦脦录脦路脧聞脦碌脧聜 脦禄脦炉脧聝脧聞脦碌脧聜</string>
    <string name="unordered_list_char_dash">脦聽脦卤脧聧脦禄脦卤 (-)</string>
    <string name="unordered_list_char_asterisk">脦聭脧聝脧聞脦碌脧聛脦炉脧聝脦潞脦驴脧聜 (*)</string>
    <string name="unordered_list_char_plus">脦拢脧聟脦陆 (+)</string>
    <string name="filemanager_doesnot_supply_required_data__appspecific">脦陇脦驴 Portal 脦录脧聙脦驴脧聛脦碌脦炉 脦陆脦卤 脦碌脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脧聞脦碌脦炉 脦录脧聦脦陆脦驴 脧聞脦驴脧聙脦鹿脦潞脦卢, offline 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脦赂脦颅脧聝脦鹿脦录脦卤 脦颅脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦卤 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脧聟脧聙脦驴脧聝脧聞脦路脧聛脦炉脦露脦碌脦鹿 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脧聡脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦颅脧聜 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脧聣脦陆 脧聙脦驴脧聟 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脧聙脦卤脧聛脦颅脧聡脦驴脧聟脦陆 脧聞脦路脦陆 脧聙脦禄脦庐脧聛脦路 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脦麓脧聛脦驴脦录脦庐 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟.</string>
    <string name="file_does_not_exist_and_cant_be_created">脦聢脦陆脦卤 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脦庐 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴脧聜 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脧聟脧聙脦卢脧聛脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脦录脧聙脦驴脧聛脦碌脦炉 脦陆脦卤 脦麓脦路脦录脦鹿脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦路脦赂脦碌脦炉</string>
    <string name="permissions">脦聰脦鹿脦潞脦卤脦鹿脧聨脦录脦卤脧聞脦卤</string>
    <string name="permission_paths_revert">脦聲脧聙脦卤脦陆脦卤脧聠脦驴脧聛脦卢 脧聞脧聣脦陆 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦驴脦鲁脧聨脦陆;</string>
    <string name="permission_not_granted">脦聠脦麓脦碌脦鹿脦卤 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脦碌脦潞脧聡脧聣脧聛脦庐脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌</string>
    <string name="sync_to_local_folder_notice">脦拢脦路脦录脦碌脦炉脧聣脧聝脦路: 脦聼脦鹿 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦颅脧聜 脧聝脧聟脦鲁脧聡脧聛脦驴脦陆脦鹿脧聝脦录脦驴脧聧 脦录脧聙脦驴脧聛脦驴脧聧脦陆 脦陆脦卤 脧聞脦驴脧聙脦驴脦赂脦碌脧聞脦驴脧聧脦陆 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦卤 脧聝脦碌 脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聝脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脧聝脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟脧聜 脧聠脦卤脦潞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聟脧聜. 脦聭脦陆脦驴脦炉脦戮脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦卤 脦卤脦禄脦禄脦卢脦露脦驴脦陆脧聞脦卤脧聜 脦卤脦陆脦卤脦禄脧聦脦鲁脧聣脧聜 脧聞脦驴 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴 脦碌脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脧聣脦陆 脧聞脦驴脧聟 Portal, 脦庐 脧聝脦碌 脦卢脦禄脦禄脦驴 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脧聡脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦庐 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脧聣脦陆.</string>
    <string name="vertical_alignment">脦職脦卤脧聞脦卤脦潞脧聦脧聛脧聟脧聠脦路 脧聝脧聞脦驴脦炉脧聡脦鹿脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="horizontal_alignment">脦聼脧聛脦鹿脦露脧聦脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦卤 脧聝脧聞脦驴脦炉脧聡脦鹿脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="default_">脦聽脧聛脦驴脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦庐</string>
    <string name="left">脦聭脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦碌脧聛脦卢</string>
    <string name="right">脦聰脦碌脦戮脦鹿脦卢</string>
    <string name="top">脦聽脦卢脦陆脧聣</string>
    <string name="bottom">脦職脦卢脧聞脧聣</string>
    <string name="center">脦職脦颅脦陆脧聞脧聛脦驴</string>
    <string name="actionbutton_spacing">脦聭脧聙脧聦脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路 ActionButton</string>
    <string name="horizontal_space_between_actionbuttons">脦聼脧聛脦鹿脦露脧聦脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦驴 脦麓脦鹿脦卢脧聝脧聞脦路脦录脦卤 脦录脦碌脧聞脦卤脦戮脧聧 ActionButtons</string>
    <string name="center_text">脦職脦碌脦陆脧聞脧聛脦卤脧聛脦鹿脧聝脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴 脦潞脦碌脦炉脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴</string>
    <string name="edit_text_in_center_of_screen">脦聲脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦炉脦卤 脦潞脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脦潞脦颅脦陆脧聞脧聛脦驴 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦驴脦赂脧聦脦陆脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="clipboard">脦聽脧聛脧聦脧聡脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦驴</string>
    <string name="select_existing_document">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦颅脦戮脧聞脦碌 脧聟脧聙脦卢脧聛脧聡脦驴脦陆 脦颅脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦驴</string>
    <string name="open_source_licenses">脦聠脦麓脦碌脦鹿脦碌脧聜 脦聭脦陆脦驴脦鹿脧聡脧聞脦驴脧聧 脦職脧聨脦麓脦鹿脦潞脦卤</string>
    <string name="rate_this_app">脦聮脦卤脦赂脦录脦驴脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脦卤脧聟脧聞脦庐脦陆 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐</string>
    <string name="translate">脦聹脦碌脧聞脦卢脧聠脧聛脦卤脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="more_info_and_help">脦聽脦碌脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聝脧聦脧聞脦碌脧聛脦碌脧聜 脧聙脦禄脦路脧聛脦驴脧聠脦驴脧聛脦炉脦碌脧聜 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦虏脦驴脦庐脦赂脦碌脦鹿脦卤</string>
    <string name="report_bugs">脦聭脦陆脦卤脧聠脦驴脧聛脦卢 脧聝脧聠脦卤脦禄脦录脦卢脧聞脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="join_community">脦聯脦炉脦陆脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦录脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聜 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦職脦驴脦鹿脦陆脧聦脧聞脦路脧聞脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="bug_reports_suggest_improvements">脦聰脧聨脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聝脧聡脧聦脦禄脦鹿脦卤, 脦卤脦陆脦卤脧聠脦驴脧聛脦卢 脧聝脧聠脦卤脦禄脦录脦卢脧聞脧聣脦陆 脦庐 脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聞脦碌脦炉脦陆脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦虏脦碌脦禄脧聞脦鹿脧聨脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聜</string>
    <string name="help_translating_this_app">脦聹脦碌脧聞脦卢脧聠脧聛脦卤脧聝脦路 脦卤脧聟脧聞脦庐脧聜 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜 脧聝脦碌 脦卢脦禄脦禄脦碌脧聜 脦鲁脦禄脧聨脧聝脧聝脦碌脧聜</string>
    <string name="source_code">脦聽脦路脦鲁脦卤脦炉脦驴脧聜 脦職脧聣脦麓脦鹿脦潞脧聦脧聜</string>
    <string name="project_license">脦聠脦麓脦碌脦鹿脦卤 脦聢脧聛脦鲁脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="contribute_code_to_this_project_anybody_welcome">脦拢脧聟脦陆脦碌脦鹿脧聝脧聠脦颅脧聛脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦潞脧聨脦麓脦鹿脦潞脦卤 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脦颅脧聛脦鲁脦驴. 脦聦脦禄脦驴脦鹿 脦碌脦炉脦陆脦卤脦鹿 脦碌脧聟脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦麓脦碌脦潞脧聞脦驴脦鹿 脦陆脦卤 脧聞脦驴 脦潞脦卢脦陆脦驴脧聟脦陆, 脧聝脧聟脦录脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦禄脦卤脦录脦虏脦卤脦陆脦驴脦录脦颅脦陆脧聣脦陆 脧聞脧聣脦陆 脦陆脦碌脦驴脦碌脦鹿脧聝脦碌脧聛脧聡脧聦脦录脦碌脦陆脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="project_team">脦聼脦录脦卢脦麓脦卤 脦聢脧聛脦鲁脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="contributors_public_add_yourself_description">脦聲脦录脧聠脦卢脦陆脦鹿脧聝脦路 脧聙脦禄脦路脧聛脦驴脧聠脦驴脧聛脦鹿脧聨脦陆 脧聝脧聟脦陆脦碌脦鹿脧聝脧聠脦颅脧聛脦驴脦陆脧聞脦驴脧聜. 脦聰脧聨脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴 脦陆脦卤 脦碌脦录脧聠脦卤脦陆脦炉脦露脦碌脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脦碌脦麓脧聨 脧聝脦碌 脦虏脦卢脧聝脦路 opt-in 脦录脦碌脧聞脦卢 脧聞脦路 脧聝脧聟脦录脦虏脦驴脦禄脦庐</string>
    <string name="descending">脧聠脦赂脦炉脦陆脦驴脧聟脧聝脦卤</string>
    <string name="ascending">脦卤脧聧脦戮脦驴脧聟脧聝脦卤</string>
    <string name="disable_spelling_underline">脦聭脧聙脦碌脦陆脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦驴脧聙脦驴脦炉脦路脧聝脦路 脦驴脧聛脦赂脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦鹿脦潞脦驴脧聧 脦碌脦禄脦颅脦鲁脧聡脦驴脧聟 脧聟脧聙脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卢脦录脦录脦鹿脧聝脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="spellcheck_keyboard_suggestion_stay_red_underline_vanishes">脦聰脦鹿脦卤脧聞脦庐脧聛脦路脧聝脦路 脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聞脦卢脧聝脦碌脧聣脦陆 脧聙脦禄脦路脦潞脧聞脧聛脦驴脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦炉脦驴脧聟, 脦路 脦潞脧聦脦潞脦潞脦鹿脦陆脦路 脧聟脧聙脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卢脦录脦录脦鹿脧聝脦路 脦碌脦戮脦卤脧聠脦卤脦陆脦炉脦露脦碌脧聞脦卤脦鹿</string>
    <string name="location">脦陇脦驴脧聙脦驴脦赂脦碌脧聝脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="text_lines">脦聯脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦颅脧聜 脦職脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="text_characters">脦搂脦卤脧聛脦卤脦潞脧聞脦庐脧聛脦碌脧聜 脦職脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="text_words">脦聸脦颅脦戮脦碌脦鹿脧聜 脦職脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="directory">脦職脦卤脧聞脦卢脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="recently_viewed_documents">脦聢脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦卤 脧聙脦驴脧聟 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦虏脦禄脦庐脦赂脦路脦潞脦卤脦陆 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脧聠脦卤脧聞脦卤</string>
    <string name="details">脦聸脦碌脧聙脧聞脦驴脦录脦颅脧聛脦碌脦鹿脦碌脧聜</string>
    <string name="calendar">脦聴脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦禄脧聦脦鲁脦鹿脦驴</string>
    <string name="warning_disallowed_sd_access">脦聽脧聛脦驴脦碌脦鹿脦麓脦驴脧聙脦驴脦炉脦路脧聝脦路! 脦聴 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脦颅脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦卢脦麓脦碌脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌脧聧脧聝脦碌脦鹿 脦卤脧聟脧聞脧聦 脧聞脦驴 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴, 脧聦脦禄脦碌脧聜 脦驴脦鹿 脦卤脦禄脦禄脦卤脦鲁脦颅脧聜 脦赂脦卤 脧聡脦卤脦赂脦驴脧聧脦陆. 脦聰脦碌脦陆 脧聟脧聙脦卢脧聛脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脦潞脦卤脦录脦炉脦卤 脦麓脧聟脦陆脦卤脧聞脧聦脧聞脦路脧聞脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脧聧脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴 脧聙脧聛脧聦脦虏脦禄脦路脦录脦卤 脦庐 脦陆脦卤 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦虏脦碌脦虏脦卤脦鹿脧聨脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦潞脦卢脧聞脦鹿, 脧聞脦驴 Android 脦卤脧聛脦陆脦碌脦炉脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦卤脦麓脦庐脧聙脦驴脧聞脦碌 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路 脦碌脦麓脧聨.</string>
    <string name="error_picture_selection">脦聰脦碌脦陆 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦颅脧聡脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌 脦碌脦鹿脦潞脧聦脦陆脦卤, 脦禄脦庐脧聠脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌 脦庐 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌脧聧脧聞脦路脦潞脦碌.</string>
    <string name="gallery_picture">脦聲脦鹿脦潞脧聦脦陆脦卤 脧聝脧聟脦禄脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="camera_picture">脦聲脦鹿脦潞脧聦脦陆脦卤 脧聠脧聣脧聞脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦鹿脦潞脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="enable_undo_and_redo_be_patient">脦聲脦陆脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦鹿脧聜 脦碌脦陆脦颅脧聛脦鲁脦碌脦鹿脦碌脧聜 脦卤脦陆脦卤脦炉脧聛脦碌脧聝脦路脧聜 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦碌脧聙脦卤脦陆脦卢脦禄脦路脧聢脦路脧聜. 脦職脦卤脧聞脦卢脦禄脦禄脦路脦禄脦驴 脦录脧聦脦陆脦驴 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聡脧聣脧聛脦路脦录脦颅脦陆脦路 脧聡脧聛脦庐脧聝脦路, 脦陆脦卤 脦碌脦炉脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聟脧聙脦驴脦录脦驴脦陆脦碌脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦驴脦炉 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脦录脦路脦陆 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聢脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦潞脦卢脧聞脦鹿 脧聝脦路脦录脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脧聦. 脦職脦禄脦碌脦炉脧聝脧聞脦碌 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦卤脦陆脦驴脦炉脦戮脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴脦陆 脦碌脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脧聞脦庐 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脦潞脦卤脦赂脦卤脧聛脦炉脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴 脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦驴脧聛脦鹿脦潞脧聦.</string>
    <string name="description">脦聽脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦庐</string>
    <string name="edit_picture">脦聲脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦炉脦卤 脦碌脦鹿脦潞脧聦脦陆脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="math">脦聹脦卤脦赂脦路脦录脦卤脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卢</string>
    <string name="enter_yaml_front_matter_attributes_to_show">脦職脦卤脧聞脦卤脧聡脧聣脧聛脦庐脦赂脦路脦潞脦卤脦陆 脧聡脦卤脧聛脦卤脦潞脧聞脦路脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卢 YAML Front Matter 脧聝脧聞脦路脦陆 脦潞脦驴脧聛脧聟脧聠脦庐 脧聞脧聣脦陆 脦碌脦录脧聠脦卤脦陆脦鹿脦露脧聦脦录脦碌脦陆脧聣脦陆 脦碌脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脧聣脦陆. 脦聲脦鹿脧聝脦卢脦鲁脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦潞脦禄脦碌脦鹿脦麓脦鹿脦卢 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脧聡脧聣脧聛脦鹿脧聝脦录脦颅脦陆脦卤 脦录脦碌 脦潞脧聦脦录脦录脦卤脧聞脦卤. 脦聭脧聠脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脦潞脦碌脦陆脧聦 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脧聞脦炉脧聙脦驴脧聞脦卤 脦庐 脧聡脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴 \'*\' 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脧聦脦禄脦卤. \n\n脦聲脦卢脦陆 脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦驴脦麓脦庐脧聙脦驴脧聞脦碌 脧聡脦卤脧聛脦卤脦潞脧聞脦路脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦鹿脦潞脧聦 脦驴脧聛脦炉脦露脦碌脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脦颅脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦驴 (脦麓脦路脦禄. 脧聞脦炉脧聞脦禄脦驴脧聜: \'脦聯脦碌脦鹿脦卤 脧聝脦卤脧聜\') 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脧聟脧聙脦卢脧聛脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脧聞脦驴 {{ post.title }} 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脦颅脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脧聦 脧聝脦卤脧聜 脧聞脧聦脧聞脦碌 脦卤脧聟脧聞脧聦 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脦赂脦炉脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聞脦卤脦鹿. 脦聹脧聙脦驴脧聛脦碌脦炉脧聞脦碌 脦陆脦卤 脦潞脦卢脦陆脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦录脦鹿脦卤 脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聝脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脧聝脦录脦颅脦陆脦路 脦潞脦碌脧聠脦卤脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤 Front Matter 脦录脦碌 脦卤脧聟脧聞脧聦脦陆 脧聞脦驴脦陆 脧聞脧聛脧聦脧聙脦驴.</string>
    <string name="table_of_contents">脦聽脦炉脦陆脦卤脦潞脦卤脧聜 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦碌脧聡脦驴脦录脦颅脦陆脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="miscellaneous">脦聰脦鹿脦卢脧聠脦驴脧聛脦卤</string>
    <string name="prefer_view">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聞脦鹿脦录脧聨脦录脦碌脦陆脦路 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦虏脦驴脦禄脦庐</string>
    <string name="no_calendar_app_is_installed">脦聰脦碌脦陆 脧聟脧聙脦卢脧聛脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脦碌脦鲁脦潞脦卤脧聞脦碌脧聝脧聞脦路脦录脦颅脦陆脦路 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐 脦路脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦炉脦驴脧聟!</string>
    <string name="popular_documents">脦聰脦路脦录脦驴脧聠脦鹿脦禄脦庐 脦颅脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦卤</string>
    <string name="color">脦搂脧聛脧聨脦录脦卤</string>
    <string name="basic_color_scheme">脦拢脧聡脦颅脦麓脦鹿脦驴 脦虏脦卤脧聝脦鹿脦潞脧聨脦陆 脧聡脧聛脧聣脦录脦卢脧聞脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="background_foreground_color_in_editor_works_dark_light">脦聭脦禄脦禄脦卢脦露脦碌脦鹿 脧聞脦驴 脧聡脧聛脧聨脦录脦卤 脧聠脧聦脦陆脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聝脦潞脦路脦陆脦炉脦驴脧聟 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦碌脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脧聞脦庐 脦潞脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟. 脦隆脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脦露脦碌脦鹿 脧聞脦驴 脦赂脦颅脦录脦卤 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦碌脦炉脦陆脦卤脦鹿 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脦赂脦颅脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴 脧聝脦碌 脦卤脦陆脦驴脦鹿脧聡脧聞脧聦 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脧聝脦潞脦驴脧聧脧聛脦驴 脦赂脦颅脦录脦卤. 脦陇脦卤 脧聡脧聛脧聨脦录脦卤脧聞脦卤 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脧聝脦庐脦录脦卤脦陆脧聝脦路脧聜 
 脧聙脦卤脧聛脦卤脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟脦陆 脧聞脦卤 脦炉脦麓脦鹿脦卤.</string>
    <string name="preset">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聛脧聟脦赂脦录脦鹿脧聝脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴</string>
    <string name="foreground">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脦潞脦庐脦陆脦鹿脦驴</string>
    <string name="background">脦楼脧聙脧聦脦虏脦卤脦赂脧聛脦驴</string>
    <string name="set_foreground_or_background_color_hexcolor_also_possible">脦聼脧聛脦炉脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴 脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聝脦潞脦庐脦陆脦鹿脦驴 脦庐 脧聞脦驴 脧聡脧聛脧聨脦录脦卤 脧聠脧聦脦陆脧聞脦驴脧聟 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦潞脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟? 脦聲脦炉脦陆脦卤脦鹿 脦碌脧聙脦炉脧聝脦路脧聜 脦麓脧聟脦陆脦卤脧聞脦庐 脦路 脦碌脦鹿脧聝脦卤脦鲁脧聣脦鲁脦庐 脦麓脦碌脦潞脦卤脦碌脦戮脦卤脦麓脦鹿脦潞脦驴脧聧 脧聡脧聛脧聣脦录脦卤脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦驴脧聧 脦潞脧聨脦麓脦鹿脦潞脦卤.</string>
    <string name="type">脦陇脧聧脧聙脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="folder">脦娄脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="folder_is_created_without_extension">- 脦聼 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴脧聜 脦麓脦路脦录脦鹿脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦碌脦炉脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脧聡脧聣脧聛脦炉脧聜 脦碌脧聙脦颅脦潞脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="keep_existing_file">- 脦陇脦卤 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦卤 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦驴脦鹿 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴脦鹿 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脦赂脦炉脧聝脧聞脦卤脦陆脧聞脦卤脦鹿</string>
    <string name="multiple_windows">脦聽脦驴脦禄脦禄脦卤脧聙脦禄脦卢 脧聙脦卤脧聛脦卢脦赂脧聟脧聛脦卤</string>
    <string name="font">脦聯脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦卤脧聞脦驴脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦卢</string>
    <string name="open_new_documents_always_in_new_window">脦聠脦陆脦驴脦鹿脦鲁脦录脦卤 脦碌脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脧聣脦陆 脧聙脦卢脦陆脧聞脦卤 脧聝脦碌 脦戮脦碌脧聡脧聣脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦卢 脧聙脦卤脧聛脦卢脦赂脧聟脧聛脦卤. 脦聭脦禄脦禄脦卢脦戮脧聞脦碌 脧聡脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脧聨脦陆脧聞脦卤脧聜 脧聞脦驴 脧聙脦禄脦庐脦潞脧聞脧聛脦驴 \'脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脧聠脦卤脧聞脦卤\' 脧聞脦路脧聜 脧聝脧聟脧聝脦潞脦碌脧聟脦庐脧聜 脧聝脦卤脧聜.</string>
    <string name="enter_or_select_format">脦聲脦鹿脧聝脦卢脦鲁脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦庐 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦颅脦戮脧聞脦碌 脦录脦驴脧聛脧聠脦庐</string>
    <string name="pick_date">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦颅脦戮脧聞脦碌 脦路脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="pick_time">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦颅脦戮脧聞脦碌 脧聨脧聛脦卤</string>
    <string name="get_format_instead_date_or_time">脦搂脧聛脦庐脧聝脦路 脦录脦驴脧聛脧聠脦庐脧聜 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦炉 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦路脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤 脦庐 脧聨脧聛脦卤</string>
    <string name="result">脦聭脧聙脦驴脧聞脦颅脦禄脦碌脧聝脦录脦卤</string>
    <string name="just_time">脦聹脧聦脦陆脦驴 脧聨脧聛脦卤</string>
    <string name="just_date">脦聹脧聦脦陆脦驴 脦路脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="last_used">脦搂脧聛脦庐脧聝脦路 脧聞脦碌脦禄脦碌脧聟脧聞脦卤脦炉脦卤脧聜 脦录脦驴脧聛脧聠脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="my_note">脦路_脧聝脦路脦录脦碌脦炉脧聣脧聝脦路_脦录脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="close">脦職脦禄脦碌脦炉脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴</string>
    <string name="cancel">脦聭脦潞脧聧脧聛脧聣脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="app_start_tab">脦聲脦潞脦潞脦炉脦陆脦路脧聝脦路 脦潞脦卤脧聛脧聞脦颅脦禄脦卤脧聜 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="tab_to_select_at_start">脦職脦卤脧聛脧聞脦颅脦禄脦卤 脧聙脦驴脧聟 脦赂脦卤 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦碌脦鲁脦碌脦炉 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脦潞脦潞脦炉脦陆脦路脧聝脦路 脧聞脦路脧聜 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="swipe_to_change_mode">脦拢脧聧脧聛脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦卤脦禄脦禄脦卤脦鲁脦庐 脦禄脦碌脦鹿脧聞脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="swipe_to_change_to_edit_or_view_mode">脦拢脧聧脧聛脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦卤脦禄脦禄脦卤脦鲁脦庐 脧聝脦碌 脦禄脦碌脦鹿脧聞脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤 脦碌脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦炉脦卤脧聜 脦庐 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦虏脦驴脦禄脦庐脧聜 (脦卤脦陆脧聞脦炉脦赂脦碌脧聞脦卤 脦卤脧聙脧聦 脧聞脦路脦陆 脧聞脧聛脦颅脧聡脦驴脧聟脧聝脦卤 脦禄脦碌脦鹿脧聞脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤)</string>
    <string name="folder_first">脦聽脧聛脧聨脧聞脦卤 脦驴 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="go_to">脦聹脦碌脧聞脦卢脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路 脧聝脦碌</string>
    <string name="appdata_public">AppData (public)</string>
    <string name="appdata_private">AppData (脦鹿脦麓脦鹿脧聣脧聞脦鹿脦潞脧聦)</string>
    <string name="appdata_sdcard">AppData (脦職脦卢脧聛脧聞脦卤 SD)</string>
    <string name="internal_storage">脦聲脧聝脧聣脧聞脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦潞脧聦脧聜 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌脧聟脧聞脦鹿脦潞脧聦脧聜 脧聡脧聨脧聛脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="open_the_document_from_main_view">脦聹脧聙脦驴脧聛脦碌脦炉脧聞脦碌 脦陆脦卤 脦卤脦陆脦驴脦炉脦戮脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴 脦颅脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦驴 脦卤脧聙脧聦 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦潞脧聧脧聛脦鹿脦卤 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦虏脦驴脦禄脦庐 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脦潞脦卢脧聞脧聣 脦录脦颅脧聛脦驴脧聜, 脧聞脦驴脦陆 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦路脦鲁脦路脧聞脦庐 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脧聣脦陆 脦庐 脧聞脦驴脦陆 脦碌脦潞脦潞脦鹿脦陆脦路脧聞脦庐. 脦楼脧聙脦卢脧聛脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脦碌脧聙脦炉脧聝脦路脧聜 脦录脦鹿脦卤 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦庐 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脧聞脦路脦陆 脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聝脦赂脦庐脦潞脦路 脦潞脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟 脧聙脦驴脧聟 脦潞脦驴脦鹿脦陆脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦庐脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌 脧聝脧聞脦驴 Portal.</string>
    <string name="notebook_is_the_home_of_your_files">脦拢脦路脦录脦碌脦鹿脧聣脦录脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聛脦鹿脦驴 脦碌脦炉脦陆脦卤脦鹿 脦驴 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴脧聜 脧聙脦驴脧聟 脧聞脦驴 Portal 脧聠脦驴脧聛脧聞脧聨脦陆脦碌脦鹿 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脧聙脧聛脧聦脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦卤 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦庐脦鲁脦路脧聝脦路脧聜 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脧聣脦陆 脧聦脧聞脦卤脦陆 脦戮脦碌脦潞脦鹿脦陆脦卢 脦路 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐. 脦聲脦炉脦陆脦卤脦鹿 脦驴 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦鹿脦潞脧聦脧聜 脧聠脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴脧聜 脧聞脧聣脦陆 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脧聣脦陆 脧聝脦卤脧聜.</string>
    <string name="quicknote_is_the_fastest_option_to_write_down_notes">脦陇脦驴 QuickNote 脦碌脦炉脦陆脦卤脦鹿 脦路 脧聞脦卤脧聡脧聧脧聞脦碌脧聛脦路 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦庐 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦碌脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦庐 脧聝脦路脦录脦碌脦鹿脧聨脧聝脦碌脧聣脦陆. 脦聲脦炉脦陆脦卤脦鹿 脦颅脦陆脦卤 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脧聝脦碌 脦录脦驴脧聛脧聠脦庐 Markdown 脦录脦碌 脧聞脦路脦陆 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦碌脦鲁脦录脦颅脦陆脦路 脧聞脦驴脧聙脦驴脦赂脦碌脧聝脦炉脦卤 &gt;Notebook/QuickNote. d&lt;, 脦录脧聙脦驴脧聛脦碌脦炉脧聞脦碌 脦陆脦卤 脦驴脧聛脦炉脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦颅脦陆脦卤 脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聝脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脧聝脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脧聝脧聞脦鹿脧聜 脧聛脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聜.</string>
    <string name="todo_is_the_easiest_way_">脦聰脦鹿脦卤脧聡脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦碌脦炉脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦鹿脧聜 脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦炉脦碌脧聜 脧聝脦卤脧聜 脦录脦碌 ToDo. 脦聲脦炉脦陆脦卤脦鹿 脦颅脦陆脦卤 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脧聝脦碌 脦录脦驴脧聛脧聠脦庐 todo.txt 脦录脦碌 脧聞脦路脦陆 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦碌脦鲁脦录脦颅脦陆脦路 脧聞脦驴脧聙脦驴脦赂脦碌脧聝脦炉脦卤 &gt;Notebook/todo. xt&lt;, 脦录脧聙脦驴脧聛脦碌脦炉脧聞脦碌 脦陆脦卤 脦驴脧聛脦炉脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦录脦炉脦卤 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脦麓脧聛脦驴脦录脦庐 脧聝脧聞脦鹿脧聜 脧聛脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聜.</string>
    <string name="navigationbar_color">脦搂脧聛脧聨脦录脦卤 脦录脧聙脦卢脧聛脦卤脧聜 脧聙脦禄脦驴脦庐脦鲁脦路脧聝脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="black">脦聹脦卤脧聧脧聛脦驴</string>
    <string name="white">脦聸脦碌脧聟脦潞脧聦</string>
    <string name="view">脦聽脧聛脦驴脦虏脦驴脦禄脦庐</string>
    <string name="view_mode">脦聸脦碌脦鹿脧聞脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦虏脦驴脦禄脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="edit_mode">脦聸脦碌脦鹿脧聞脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤 脦碌脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦炉脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="mount_storage">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脦卢脧聛脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦赂. 脧聡脧聨脧聛脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="application_needs_access_to_storage_mount_it">脦聭脧聙脦卤脦鹿脧聞脦碌脦炉脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脦卢脦麓脦碌脦鹿脦卤 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路 脧聝脦碌 脦卤脧聟脧聞脧聦脦陆 脧聞脦驴脦陆 脧聡脧聨脧聛脦驴 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦赂脦庐脦潞脦碌脧聟脧聝脦路脧聜. 脦陇脦驴脧聙脦驴脦赂脦碌脧聞脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴脦陆 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌脧聟脧聞脦鹿脦潞脧聦 脧聡脧聨脧聛脦驴 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脦麓脧聨脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路. 脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦虏脦碌脦虏脦卤脦鹿脧聨脧聝脧聞脦碌 脦卤脧聟脧聞脧聦 脧聞脦驴 脧聙脦卤脧聛脦卢脦赂脧聟脧聛脦驴 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脦禄脧聦脦鲁脦驴脧聟 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脦碌脦录脧聠脦卤脦陆脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦碌脦炉 脦颅脦陆脦卤 脦卤脦陆脦卤脦麓脧聟脧聦脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴 脧聙脦卤脧聛脦卢脦赂脧聟脧聛脦驴. 脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦颅脦戮脧聞脦碌 脦碌脦潞脦碌脦炉 脧聞脦驴脦陆 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌脧聟脧聞脦鹿脦潞脧聦 脧聡脧聨脧聛脦驴 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脧聙脦卤脧聞脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦庐.</string>
    <string name="share_into">脦職脦驴脦鹿脦陆脦庐 脧聡脧聛脦庐脧聝脦路 脧聝脦碌</string>
    <string name="favourite">脦聭脦鲁脦卤脧聙脦路脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴</string>
    <string name="favourites">脦聭脦鲁脦卤脧聙脦路脦录脦颅脦陆脦卤</string>
    <string name="please_wait">脦聽脦卤脧聛脦卤脦潞脦卤脦禄脧聨 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦碌脧聞脦碌</string>
    <string name="app_start_folder">脦娄脦卢脦潞脦碌脦禄脦驴脧聜 脦颅脦陆脦卤脧聛脦戮脦路脧聜 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="tab_width">脦聹脦颅脦鲁脦碌脦赂脦驴脧聜 脧聝脧聞脦路脦禄脦驴脦赂脦颅脧聞脦路</string>
    <string name="amount_of_space_for_tab">脦聽脦驴脧聝脧聦 脦潞脦碌脦陆脧聨脦陆 脧聡脦卤脧聛脦卤脦潞脧聞脦庐脧聛脧聣脦陆 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦碌脦录脧聠脦卢脦陆脦鹿脧聝脦路 脧聝脧聞脦路脦禄脦驴脦赂脦颅脧聞脦路</string>
    <string name="selected_file_may_be_a_textfile_want_to_open_in_editor">脦陇脦驴 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦碌脦鲁脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脦录脧聙脦驴脧聛脦碌脦炉 脦陆脦卤 脦碌脦炉脦陆脦卤脦鹿 脦颅脦陆脦卤 脦卤脧聙脦禄脧聦 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脦潞脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟. 脦聵脦颅脦禄脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦陆脦卤 脧聞脦驴 脦卤脦陆脦驴脦炉脦戮脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聝脧聞脦驴脦陆 脦碌脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脧聞脦庐, 脦庐 脧聝脦碌 脦卢脦禄脦禄脦路 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐?\n\n脦聹脦路脦陆 脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聝脧聙脦卤脦赂脦庐脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦陆脦卤 脦卤脦陆脦驴脦炉脦戮脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦麓脧聟脦卤脦麓脦鹿脦潞脦卢 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦卤. 脦聭脦陆 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脦碌脦炉脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聝脦炉脦鲁脦驴脧聟脧聛脦驴脦鹿, 脦卤脦陆脦驴脦炉脦戮脧聞脦碌 脦录脦碌 脦卢脦禄脦禄脦路 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐.</string>
    <string name="list_in_recent_files">脦聸脦炉脧聝脧聞脦卤 脧聝脦碌 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脧聠脦卤脧聞脦卤 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="reload">脦聲脧聙脦卤脦陆脦卤脧聠脧聦脧聛脧聞脧聣脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="wrap_words">脦聭脦陆脦卤脦麓脦炉脧聙脦禄脧聣脧聝脦路 脦禄脦颅脦戮脦碌脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="soft_break_if_not_fit_to_width_else_enable_horizontal_scrolling">Soft break if text doesn\'t fit to screen width. Else enable horizontal scrolling.</string>
    <string name="always_open_with_this_app">脦聽脦卢脦陆脧聞脦卤 脦卢脦陆脦驴脦鹿脦鲁脦录脦卤 脦录脦碌 脦卤脧聟脧聞脦庐脦陆 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐</string>
    <string name="always_open_files_with_this_app_when_list_contains_file_extension">脦聽脦卢脦陆脧聞脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脦卤脦陆脦驴脦炉脦鲁脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦卤 脦录脦碌 脦卤脧聟脧聞脦庐脦陆 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐, 脧聦脧聞脦卤脦陆 脦路 脦禄脦炉脧聝脧聞脦卤 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦颅脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脧聙脦颅脦潞脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟. 脦搂脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 \'脦職脦卤脦陆脦颅脦陆脦卤, .html, . ss , .js\' 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脧聙脦卤脧聛脦卢脦麓脦碌脦鹿脦鲁脦录脦卤, 脦卤脦陆 脦赂脦颅脦禄脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦陆脦卤 脦碌脧聙脦碌脦戮脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脧聞脦碌脦炉脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦卤 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦卤 web 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦卤脧聟脧聞脦卢 脧聡脧聣脧聛脦炉脧聜 脦碌脧聙脦颅脦潞脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟.</string>
    <string name="open_file_with">脦聠脦陆脦驴脦鹿脦鲁脦录脦卤 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟 脦录脦碌</string>
    <string name="rotate">脦聽脦碌脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脧聛脦驴脧聠脦庐</string>
    <string name="template">脦聽脧聛脧聦脧聞脧聟脧聙脦驴</string>
    <string name="send_debug_log">脦聭脧聙脦驴脧聝脧聞脦驴脦禄脦庐 脦職脦卤脧聞脦卤脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦庐脧聜 脦聭脧聙脦驴脧聝脧聠脦卤脦禄脦录脦卢脧聞脧聣脧聝脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="print_pdf">Print / PDF</string>
    <string name="bigger_headings">脦聹脦碌脦鲁脦卤脦禄脧聧脧聞脦碌脧聛脦碌脧聜 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦潞脦碌脧聠脦卤脦禄脦炉脦麓脦碌脧聜</string>
    <string name="increase_text_size_of_headings_according_to_level">脦聭脧聧脦戮脦路脧聝脦路 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦录脦碌脦鲁脦颅脦赂脦驴脧聟脧聜 脦潞脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟 脧聞脧聣脦陆 脦潞脦碌脧聠脦卤脦禄脦炉脦麓脧聣脦陆 脦卤脦陆脦卢脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦卤 脦录脦碌 脧聞脦驴 脦碌脧聙脦炉脧聙脦碌脦麓脦驴 (# h1, ## h2. ## h3芒聙娄)</string>
    <string name="current">脦陇脧聛脦颅脧聡脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="record_audio">脦聲脦鲁脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦庐 脦聣脧聡脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="attach">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脧聝脧聧脦陆脦卤脧聢脦路</string>
    <string name="copy_file">脦聭脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦庐 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="page">脦拢脦碌脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤</string>
    <string name="experimental_features">脦聽脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦卤脦录脦卤脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卢 脧聡脦卤脧聛脦卤脦潞脧聞脦路脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卢</string>
    <string name="tools">脦聲脧聛脦鲁脦卤脦禄脦碌脦炉脦卤</string>
    <string name="reading">脦聭脦陆脦卢脦鲁脦陆脧聣脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="read">脦聭脦陆脦卢脦鲁脦陆脧聣脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="table">脦聽脦炉脦陆脦卤脦潞脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="how_much_columns_press_table_button_long_to_start_table">脦聽脧聦脧聝脦碌脧聜 脧聝脧聞脦庐脦禄脦碌脧聜? 脦聽脦卤脧聞脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴 脦潞脦驴脧聟脦录脧聙脦炉 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脧聙脦炉脦陆脦卤脦潞脦卤 脧聙脦卤脧聛脦卤脧聞脦碌脧聞脦卤脦录脦颅脦陆脦卤 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脦戮脦碌脦潞脦鹿脦陆脦庐脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦颅脦陆脦卤脦陆 脧聙脦炉脦陆脦卤脦潞脦卤 (脦碌脦鹿脧聝脦卤脦鲁脧聣脦鲁脦庐 脦潞脦碌脧聠脦卤脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤脧聜), 脧聙脦卤脧聞脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聝脧聧脦陆脧聞脦驴脦录脦卤 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聝脦赂脦颅脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦录脦鹿脦卤 脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦庐.</string>
    <string name="example_of_a_markdown_table">脦聽脦卤脧聛脦卢脦麓脦碌脦鹿脦鲁脦录脦卤 脧聙脦炉脦陆脦卤脦潞脦卤 Markdown</string>
    <string name="delete_lines">脦聰脦鹿脦卤脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦庐 脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脧聨脦陆</string>
    <string name="unordered_list">脦聹脦路 脧聞脦卤脦戮脦鹿脦陆脦驴脦录脦路脦录脦颅脦陆脦路 脦禄脦炉脧聝脧聞脦卤</string>
    <string name="ordered_list">脦陇脦卤脦戮脦鹿脦陆脦驴脦录脦路脦录脦颅脦陆脦路 脦禄脦炉脧聝脧聞脦卤</string>
    <string name="check_list">脦聸脦炉脧聝脧聞脦卤 脦碌脦禄脦颅脦鲁脧聡脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="open_link">脦聠脦陆脦驴脦鹿脦鲁脦录脦卤 脧聝脧聟脦陆脦麓脦颅脧聝脦录脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="common_color_picker">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦颅脦卤脧聜 脧聡脧聛脧聨脦录脦卤脧聞脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="date_and_time">脦聴脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脧聨脧聛脦卤</string>
    <string name="jump_to_bottom">脦聹脦碌脧聞脦卢脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脦潞脦卢脧聞脧聣 脦录脦颅脧聛脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="quote">脦聽脦卤脧聛脦卢脦赂脦碌脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="heading">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦潞脦碌脧聠脦卤脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤</string>
    <string name="heading_1">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦潞脦碌脧聠脦卤脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤 1</string>
    <string name="heading_2">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦潞脦碌脧聠脦卤脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤 2</string>
    <string name="heading_3">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦潞脦碌脧聠脦卤脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤 3</string>
    <string name="heading_4">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦潞脦碌脧聠脦卤脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤 4</string>
    <string name="heading_5">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦潞脦碌脧聠脦卤脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤 5</string>
    <string name="heading_6">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦潞脦碌脧聠脦卤脦禄脦炉脦麓脦卤 6</string>
    <string name="bold">脦聢脦陆脧聞脦驴脦陆脦卤</string>
    <string name="italic">脦聽脦禄脦卢脦鲁脦鹿脦卤</string>
    <string name="highlighted">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脧聝脦路脦录脦卤脧聝脦录脦颅脦陆脦卤</string>
    <string name="strikeout">脦聰脦鹿脦卤脦潞脧聛脦鹿脧聞脦庐 脦聰脦鹿脦卤脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦庐</string>
    <string name="inline_code">脦聲脦录脦虏脧聦脦禄脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聜 脦潞脧聣脦麓脦鹿脦潞脧聦脧聜</string>
    <string name="horizontal_line">脦聼脧聛脦鹿脦露脧聦脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦卤 脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦庐</string>
    <string name="toggle_done">脦聲脦陆脦卤脦禄脦禄脦卤脦鲁脦庐 脦驴脦禄脦驴脦潞脦禄脦路脧聛脧聣脦录脦颅脦陆脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="link_color">脦搂脧聛脧聨脦录脦卤 脧聝脧聟脦陆脦麓脦颅脧聝脦录脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="add_context">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脦赂脦庐脦潞脦路 脧聝脧聟脦鲁脦潞脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="add_project">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脦赂脦庐脦潞脦路 脦颅脧聛脦鲁脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="archive_completed_tasks">脦聭脧聛脧聡脦碌脦鹿脦驴脦赂脦颅脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脦驴脦禄脦驴脦潞脦禄脦路脧聛脧聣脦录脦颅脦陆脧聣脦陆 脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦鹿脧聨脦陆</string>
    <string name="create_new_file_or_folder">脦聰脦路脦录脦鹿脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤 脦陆脦颅脦驴脧聟 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟 脦庐 脧聠脦卤脦潞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="choose_format">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦庐 脦录脦驴脧聛脧聠脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="selected">脦聲脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦碌脦鲁脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴</string>
    <string name="back">脦聽脦炉脧聝脧聣</string>
    <string name="expand_collapse">脦聭脦陆脦卢脧聙脧聞脧聟脦戮脦路 / 脦拢脧聧脦录脧聙脧聞脧聟脦戮脦路</string>
    <string name="essential">脦聼脧聟脧聝脦鹿脦卤脧聝脧聞脦鹿脦潞脧聦</string>
    <string name="append_human_readable_uuid_to_new_tasks">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脦卢脧聛脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脦卤脦陆脦卤脦鲁脦陆脧聨脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聟 脦卤脧聙脧聦 脦卢脦陆脦赂脧聛脧聣脧聙脦驴 UUID 脧聝脦碌 脦陆脦颅脦碌脧聜 脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦卤脧聝脦炉脦碌脧聜</string>
    <string name="action_order">脦拢脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦卢 脦碌脦陆脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦碌脦鹿脧聨脦陆</string>
    <string name="toggle_action_visibility">脦聲脦陆脦卤脦禄脦禄脦卤脦鲁脦庐 脦驴脧聛脦卤脧聞脧聦脧聞脦路脧聞脦卤脧聜 脦碌脦陆脦颅脧聛脦鲁脦碌脦鹿脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="load_default_settings">脦娄脧聦脧聛脧聞脧聣脧聝脦路 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦碌脦鲁脦录脦颅脦陆脧聣脦陆 脧聛脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脧聝脦碌脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="drag">脦拢脧聧脧聛脦碌脧聞脦碌</string>
    <string name="created">脦聰脦路脦录脦鹿脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦庐脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌</string>
    <string name="file_encryption_password">脦職脧聣脦麓脦鹿脦潞脧聦脧聜 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路脧聜 脦潞脧聛脧聟脧聙脧聞脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦路脧聝脦路脧聜 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="no_password_set_cannot_encrypt_decrypt">脦聰脦碌脦陆 脦颅脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脦驴脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦碌脦炉 脦潞脧聣脦麓脦鹿脦潞脧聦脧聜 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路脧聜, 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脦录脧聙脦驴脧聛脦碌脦炉 脦陆脦卤 脦潞脧聛脧聟脧聙脧聞脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦路脦赂脦碌脦炉 脦庐 脦陆脦卤 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦潞脧聛脧聟脧聙脧聞脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦路脦赂脦碌脦炉.\n脦聹脦碌脧聞脦卤脦虏脦碌脦炉脧聞脦碌 脧聝脧聞脦鹿脧聜 脦隆脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聜 -&gt; 脦聯脦碌脦陆脦鹿脦潞脦卢 -&gt; 脦職脧聣脦麓脦鹿脦潞脧聦脧聜 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路脧聜 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脦驴脧聛脦炉脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦颅脦陆脦卤脦陆 脦潞脧聣脦麓脦鹿脦潞脧聦 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路脧聜.</string>
    <string name="encrypt_file_content">脦職脧聛脧聟脧聙脧聞脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦路脧聝脦路 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦碌脧聡脦驴脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="utf8_with_bom">UTF-8 脦录脦碌 BOM</string>
    <string name="could_not_encrypt_file_content_the_file_was_not_saved">脦聭脦麓脧聟脦陆脦卤脦录脦炉脦卤 脦潞脧聛脧聟脧聙脧聞脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦路脧聝脦路脧聜 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦碌脧聡脦驴脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟. 脦陇脦驴 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌脧聧脧聞脦路脦潞脦碌.</string>
    <string name="could_not_decrypt_file_content_wrong_password_or_is_the_file_maybe_not_encrypted">脦聰脦碌脦陆 脦庐脧聞脦卤脦陆 脦麓脧聟脦陆脦卤脧聞脦庐 脦路 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦潞脧聛脧聟脧聙脧聞脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦路脧聝脦路 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦碌脧聡脦驴脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟. 脦搂脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦碌脦炉脧聞脦碌 脦禄脦卢脦赂脦驴脧聜 脦潞脧聣脦麓脦鹿脦潞脧聦 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路脧聜? 脦聲脦炉脦陆脦卤脦鹿 脧聞脦驴 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脧聙脧聛脦卤脦鲁脦录脦卤脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卢 脦潞脧聛脧聟脧聙脧聞脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦路脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴 脦录脦碌 脦潞脧聛脧聟脧聙脧聞脦驴脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦路脧聝脦路 Portal鈥檚 AES;</string>
    <string name="password_already_set_setting_a_new_password_will_overwrite">脦聼 脦潞脧聣脦麓脦鹿脦潞脧聦脧聜 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路脧聜 脦颅脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脦庐脦麓脦路 脦驴脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦碌脦炉. 脦聼 脦驴脧聛脦鹿脧聝脦录脧聦脧聜 脦陆脦颅脦驴脧聟 脦潞脧聣脦麓脦鹿脦潞脦驴脧聧 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路脧聜 脦赂脦卤 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卤脧聝脧聞脦庐脧聝脦碌脦鹿 脧聞脦驴脦陆 脧聟脧聙脦卢脧聛脧聡脦驴脦陆脧聞脦卤 脦潞脧聣脦麓脦鹿脦潞脧聦 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路脧聜 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦碌脦陆脦麓脦颅脧聡脦碌脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脦陆脦卤 脦录脦路脦陆 脦录脧聙脦驴脧聛脦碌脦炉脧聞脦碌 脦陆脦卤 脦颅脧聡脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路 脧聝脦碌 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦卤 脧聙脦鹿脦卤 脧聝脦碌 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦炉脧聙脧聞脧聣脧聝脦路 脧聙脦驴脧聟 脦戮脦碌脧聡脦卢脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴脦陆 脦潞脧聣脦麓脦鹿脦潞脧聦 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聝脦虏脦卤脧聝脦路脧聜.</string>
    <string name="code_block">脦聹脧聙脦禄脦驴脦潞 脦潞脧聨脦麓脦鹿脦潞脦卤</string>
    <string name="add_completion_date">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脦赂脦庐脦潞脦路 脦路脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤脧聜 脦驴脦禄脦驴脦潞脦禄脦庐脧聛脧聣脧聝脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="add_completion_date_for_todos_when_marking_them_as_done">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聝脦赂脦庐脦潞脦路 脦路脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤脧聜 脦驴脦禄脦驴脦潞脦禄脦庐脧聛脧聣脧聝脦路脧聜 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 todos 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢 脧聞脦路 脧聝脦庐脦录脦卤脦陆脧聝脦庐 脧聞脦驴脧聟脧聜 脧聣脧聜 脦驴脦禄脦驴脦潞脦禄脦路脧聛脧聣脦录脦颅脦陆脦卤</string>
    <string name="file_description_format">脦聹脦驴脧聛脧聠脦庐 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦庐脧聜 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="file_description_format_dialog">脦聹脦驴脧聛脧聠脦庐 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脧聞脦路脦陆 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦庐 脦潞脦卢脧聞脧聣 脦卤脧聙脧聦 脦潞脦卢脦赂脦碌 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脧聙脧聛脧聦脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦卤 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦庐脦鲁脦路脧聝脦路脧聜 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脧聣脦陆. 脦聭脦潞脦驴脦禄脦驴脧聟脦赂脦碌脦炉 脧聞脦驴脧聟脧聜 脦潞脦卤脦陆脧聦脦陆脦碌脧聜 SimpleDateFormat 脧聞脦驴脧聟 Android, 脦录脦碌 脧聞脦路脦陆 脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聝脦赂脦庐脦潞脦路 脧聞脦驴脧聟 FS 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脦录脧聠脦卢脦陆脦鹿脧聝脦路 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦录脦碌脦鲁脦颅脦赂脦驴脧聟脧聜 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟. 脦聭脧聠脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脦潞脦碌脦陆脧聦 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脧聡脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦庐脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦路脦陆 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦碌脦鲁脦录脦颅脦陆脦路 脦录脦驴脧聛脧聠脦庐 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脧聞脦驴脦陆 脧聞脧聦脧聙脦驴 脧聝脦卤脧聜.\n\n脦聽脦卤脧聛脦卢脦麓脦碌脦鹿脦鲁脦录脦卤 脦碌脦鹿脧聝脧聦脦麓脦驴脧聟:\nFS yyyyy MMM dd hh:mm:ss aa\n脦聹脦驴脧聛脧聠脦庐 脦碌脦戮脧聦脦麓脦驴脧聟:\n30KB 2020 脦聹脦卤脧聛 20 11:24:52 脦录脦录</string>
    <string name="loading_default_value">脦娄脧聦脧聛脧聞脧聣脧聝脦路 脧聙脧聛脦驴脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦碌脦鲁脦录脦颅脦陆脦路脧聜 脧聞脦鹿脦录脦庐脧聜</string>
    <string name="file_settings">脦隆脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聜 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="search_and_replace">脦聭脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 / 脦聭脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="search_for">脦聭脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤</string>
    <string name="replace_with">脦聭脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路 脦录脦碌</string>
    <string name="replace_once">脦聭脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路 (1)</string>
    <string name="replace_all">脦聭脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路 脧聦脦禄脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="matches">脦聭脦陆脧聞脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦驴脦鹿脧聡脦炉脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聜</string>
    <string name="search_replace_pattern_error_message">脦聭脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脦庐 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路 脧聝脧聠脦卢脦禄脦录脦卤脧聞脦驴脧聜 脦录脦驴脧聞脦炉脦虏脦驴脧聟.</string>
    <string name="backup_settings">脦隆脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脧聝脦碌脦鹿脧聜 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦驴脧聟 脦卤脧聝脧聠脦卤脦禄脦碌脦炉脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="restore_settings">脦聲脧聙脦卤脦陆脦卤脧聠脦驴脧聛脦卢 脧聛脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脧聝脦碌脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="failed_to_create_backup">脦聭脧聙脦驴脧聞脧聟脧聡脦炉脦卤 脦麓脦路脦录脦鹿脦驴脧聟脧聛脦鲁脦炉脦卤脧聜 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦驴脧聟 脦卤脧聝脧聠脦卤脦禄脦碌脦炉脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="export_settings_to_json_file">脦聲脦戮脦卤脦鲁脧聣脦鲁脦庐 脧聛脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脧聝脦碌脧聣脦陆 脧聝脦碌 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 json</string>
    <string name="import_settings_from_backup_json_file_on_success_the_app_is_restarted">脦聲脦鹿脧聝脦卤脦鲁脧聣脦鲁脦庐 脧聛脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脧聝脦碌脧聣脦陆 脦卤脧聙脧聦 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦炉脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦驴 脦卤脧聝脧聠脦卤脦禄脦碌脦炉脦卤脧聜 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟 json. 脦聹脦碌 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脧聞脧聟脧聡脦炉脦卤, 脦路 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐 脦碌脧聙脦卤脦陆脦碌脦潞脦潞脦鹿脦陆脦碌脦炉脧聞脦卤脦鹿.</string>
    <string name="failed_to_restore_settings_from_backup">脦聭脧聙脦驴脧聞脧聟脧聡脦炉脦卤 脦碌脧聙脦卤脦陆脦卤脧聠脦驴脧聛脦卢脧聜 脧聛脧聟脦赂脦录脦炉脧聝脦碌脧聣脦陆 脦卤脧聙脧聦 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦炉脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦驴 脦卤脧聝脧聠脦卤脦禄脦碌脦炉脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="newline_is_new_paragraph">Newline = 脦陆脦颅脦卤 脧聙脦卤脧聛脦卢脦鲁脧聛脦卤脧聠脦驴脧聜</string>
    <string name="search_in_content">脦聭脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦碌脧聡脧聦脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴</string>
    <string name="max_search_depth">脦聮脦卢脦赂脦驴脧聜 脦卤脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="ignore_list">脦聭脦鲁脦陆脧聦脦路脧聝脦路 脦禄脦炉脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聜</string>
    <string name="do_not_search_specified_files_and_folders">脦聺脦卤 脦录脦路脦陆 脦鲁脦炉脦陆脦碌脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脦卤脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脧聝脦碌 脧聝脧聟脦鲁脦潞脦碌脦潞脧聛脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦卤 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦卤 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脧聠脦卤脦潞脦颅脦禄脦驴脧聟脧聜.\n脦搂脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦路 脦陆脦颅脦卤 脦鲁脧聛脦卤脦录脦录脦庐 脧聣脧聜 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脧聡脧聣脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦鹿脦潞脧聦.\n脦搂脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脦碌脦鹿脧聝脦卤脦鲁脧聣脦鲁脦鹿脦潞脦卢 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦卤脦潞脧聛脦鹿脦虏脦庐 脦驴脦陆脧聦脦录脦卤脧聞脦卤 dir: \"Test\".\n脦聣 脧聡脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 Regex \'芒聠聭[.].*\'\n脦聽脦卤脧聛脦卤脦麓脦碌脦炉脦鲁脦录脦卤脧聞脦卤: ^\\..*\n\"脦麓脦驴脦潞脦鹿脦录脦庐\"\n\"脦聰脦驴脦潞脦鹿脦录脦庐\"\n.*脦录脧聟脧聝脧聞脦鹿脦潞脧聦.*\n.*BACKUP.*\n.*.ini</string>
    <string name="regex_search">脦聭脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 Regex</string>
    <string name="case_sensitive">脦聰脦鹿脦卢脦潞脧聛脦鹿脧聝脦路 脧聙脦碌脦露脧聨脦陆/ 脦潞脦碌脧聠脦卤脦禄脦卤脦炉脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="stop_search_after_first_match">脦聰脦鹿脦卤脦潞脦驴脧聙脦庐 脦卤脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路脧聜 脦录脦碌脧聞脦卢 脧聞脦路脦陆 脧聙脧聛脧聨脧聞脦路 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦驴脦炉脧聡脦鹿脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="regex_can_not_be_compiled">Regex 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脦录脧聙脦驴脧聛脦碌脦炉 脦陆脦卤 脦录脦碌脧聞脦卤脦鲁脦禄脧聣脧聞脧聞脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦碌脦炉</string>
    <string name="keep_both">脦職脧聛脦卤脧聞脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脧聞脦卤 脦麓脧聧脦驴</string>
    <string name="skip">脦聽脦卤脧聛脦卢脦禄脦碌脦鹿脧聢脦路</string>
    <string name="overwrite">脦聭脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="keep_both_all">脦職脧聛脦卤脧聞脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脧聞脦卤 脦麓脧聧脦驴 (脧聦脦禄脦卤)</string>
    <string name="skip_all">脦聽脦卤脧聛脦卢脦禄脦碌脦鹿脧聢脦路 (脧聦脦禄脦卤)</string>
    <string name="overwrite_all">脦聭脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聝脧聞脦卤脧聝脦路 (脧聦脦禄脦卤)</string>
    <string name="copy_move_conflict_message">\'%1$s\' 脧聟脧聙脦卢脧聛脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脦庐脦麓脦路 脧聝脧聞脦驴 %2$s</string>
    <string name="additional_contexts_and_projects">脦聽脧聛脧聦脧聝脦赂脦碌脧聞脦卤 脧聙脦禄脦卤脦炉脧聝脦鹿脦卤 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脦颅脧聛脦鲁脦卤</string>
    <string name="enter_space_seperated_contexts_and_projects_these_will">脦聲脦鹿脧聝脦卢脦鲁脦碌脧聞脦碌 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脧聡脧聣脧聛脦鹿脧聝脦录脦颅脦陆脦卤 脦录脦碌 脦潞脦碌脦陆脦卢 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脧聝脧聞脦庐脦录脦卤脧聞脦卤 @contexts 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 +projects. 脦聭脧聟脧聞脦卢 脦赂脦卤 脦碌脦炉脦陆脦卤脦鹿 脧聙脦卢脦陆脧聞脦卤 脦驴脧聛脦卤脧聞脦卢 脧聝脧聞脦驴脧聟脧聜 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脦禄脧聦脦鲁脦驴脧聟脧聜 脦碌脦鹿脧聝脦卤脦鲁脧聣脦鲁脦庐脧聜 todo.txt.</string>
    <string name="infinite">脦聭脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脧聦脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦驴</string>
    <string name="browse_by_project">脦聭脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脦卤脦陆脦卢 脦颅脧聛脦鲁脦驴</string>
    <string name="browse_by_context">脦聽脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦庐脦鲁脦路脧聝脦路 脦卤脦陆脦卢 脧聙脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦虏脦卢脦禄脦禄脦驴脦陆</string>
    <string name="insert_project">脦聲脦鹿脧聝脦卤脦鲁脧聣脦鲁脦庐 脦颅脧聛脦鲁脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="insert_context">Insert contexts</string>
    <string name="browse_todo">脦聽脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦庐脦鲁脦路脧聝脦路 todo</string>
    <string name="browse_by_priority">脦聭脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢 脧聙脧聛脦驴脧聞脦碌脧聛脦卤脦鹿脧聦脧聞脦路脧聞脦卤</string>
    <string name="browse_by_due_date">脦聽脦碌脧聛脦鹿脦庐脦鲁脦路脧聝脦路 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢 脦路脦录脦碌脧聛脦驴脦录脦路脦陆脦炉脦卤 脦禄脦庐脦戮脦路脧聜</string>
    <string name="due_overdue">脦聲脦潞脧聙脧聛脧聦脦赂脦碌脧聝脦录脦驴</string>
    <string name="due_today">脦聸脦庐脦戮脦路 脧聝脦庐脦录脦碌脧聛脦卤</string>
    <string name="due_future">脦聲脦戮脧聦脧聠脦禄脦路脧聝脦路 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脦录脦颅脦禄脦禄脦驴脦陆</string>
    <string name="completed">脦聼脦禄脦驴脦潞脦禄脦路脧聛脧聨脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌</string>
    <string name="advanced_filtering">脦聽脧聛脦驴脦路脦鲁脦录脦颅脦陆脦卤 脧聠脦炉脦禄脧聞脧聛脦卤</string>
    <string name="match_any">脦陇脦卤脦炉脧聛脦鹿脦卤脧聝脦录脦卤 脦聼脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦驴脦麓脦庐脧聙脦驴脧聞脦碌</string>
    <string name="match_all">脦陇脦卤脦炉脧聛脦鹿脦卤脧聝脦录脦卤 脦聦脦禄脧聣脦陆</string>
    <string name="dynamic_notebook_root_links">脦聰脧聟脦陆脦卤脦录脦鹿脦潞脦庐 脦卤脦陆脦卤脦露脦庐脧聞脦路脧聝脦路 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦庐脧聜 脧聝脦路脦录脦碌脦鹿脧聣脦录脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聛脦鹿脦驴脧聟</string>
    <string name="search_dynamically_for_notebook_root">脦聯脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脦卤脦潞脦驴脦禄脦驴脧聟脦赂脦庐脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴脧聟脧聜 脧聝脧聟脦陆脦麓脦颅脧聝脦录脦驴脧聟脧聜 wiki, 脦卤脦陆脦卤脦露脦路脧聞脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脦麓脧聟脦陆脦卤脦录脦鹿脦潞脦卢 脧聞脦驴 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴 notebook.zim 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脦碌脦陆脧聞脦驴脧聙脦炉脧聝脦碌脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴脦陆 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦鹿脦潞脧聦 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦驴 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脧聞脦驴 脧聞脧聛脦颅脧聡脦驴脦陆 脧聝脦路脦录脦碌脦鹿脧聣脦录脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聛脦鹿脦驴. 脦聲脦陆脦碌脧聛脦鲁脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脦卤脧聟脧聞脦庐 脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦庐 脦卤脦陆 脧聡脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦碌脦炉脧聞脦碌 脧聙脦驴脦禄脦禄脦卢 脧聝脦路脦录脦碌脦鹿脧聣脦录脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聛脦鹿脦卤, 脦庐 脧聞脦驴脦陆 脦潞脦卤脧聞脦卢脦禄脦驴脦鲁脦驴 脧聝脦路脦录脦碌脦鹿脧聣脦录脦卤脧聞脦卤脧聛脦炉脧聣脦陆 脧聙脦驴脧聟 脦颅脧聡脦碌脦鹿 脦驴脧聛脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦碌脦炉 脧聝脧聞脦路脦陆 脦碌脧聠脦卤脧聛脦录脦驴脦鲁脦庐 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脧聝脧聞脦驴脦鹿脧聡脦碌脦炉 脧聝脧聞脦驴 zim 脧聝脦路脦录脦碌脦鹿脧聣脦录脦卤脧聞脦卢脧聛脦鹿脦驴 脧聝脦卤脧聜.</string>
    <string name="share_into_format_prefix_for_text_shared">脦娄脦驴脧聛脦录脦卢脧聞/脦聽脧聛脧聦脦赂脦碌脦录脦卤 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦潞脦碌脦炉脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴 脧聙脦驴脧聟 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脦录脦驴脦鹿脧聛脦卢脦露脦碌脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脧聝脧聞脦驴 Portal. 脦聭脦潞脦驴脦禄脦驴脧聟脦赂脦碌脦炉 脧聞脦驴脧聟脧聜 脦潞脦卤脦陆脧聦脦陆脦碌脧聜 脧聞脦驴脧聟 Android SimpleDateFormat.\n\n脦搂脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦庐脧聝脧聞脦碌 脧聞脦驴 {{text}} 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脧聞脦路 脦赂脦颅脧聝脦路 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦潞脦碌脦鹿脦录脦颅脦陆脦驴脧聟. 脦聭脦陆 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脦麓脦驴脦赂脦碌脦炉, 脧聞脦驴 脦潞脦碌脦炉脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴 脦碌脧聙脦鹿脦潞脦驴脦禄脦禄脦碌脦炉脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脦潞脦卤脦鹿 脧聞脦驴 脧聠脦驴脧聛脦录脦卢脧聞 脧聡脧聛脦路脧聝脦鹿脦录脦驴脧聙脦驴脦鹿脦碌脦炉脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脧聝脦卤脦陆 脧聙脧聛脧聦脦赂脦碌脦录脦卤.</string>
    <string name="share_into_format">脦職脦驴脦鹿脦陆脦庐 脧聡脧聛脦庐脧聝脦路 脧聝脦碌 - 脦聹脦驴脧聛脧聠脦庐</string>
    <string name="auto_format">脦聭脧聟脧聞脧聦脦录脦卤脧聞脦路 脦麓脦鹿脦卤脦录脧聦脧聛脧聠脧聣脧聝脦路</string>
    <string name="insert_snippet">脦聲脦鹿脧聝脦卤脦鲁脧聣脦鲁脦庐 脦卤脧聙脦驴脧聝脧聙脦卢脧聝脦录脦卤脧聞脦驴脧聜 脦潞脧聨脦麓脦鹿脦潞脦卤</string>
    <string name="error_could_not_open_file">脦聭脦麓脧聟脦陆脦卤脦录脦炉脦卤 脦卤脦陆脦驴脦炉脦鲁脦录脦卤脧聞脦驴脧聜 脧聞脦驴脧聟 脦卤脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦驴脧聟.</string>
    <string name="document_error_clip">脦聭脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦录脦碌脧聞脧聨脧聙脦鹿脧聝脦路 脧聝脧聠脦卢脦禄脦录脦卤脧聞脦驴脧聜: 脦陇脦驴 脦潞脦碌脦炉脦录脦碌脦陆脦驴 脦卤脦陆脧聞脦鹿脦鲁脧聛脦卢脧聠脦路脦潞脦碌 脧聝脧聞脦驴 脧聙脧聛脧聦脧聡脦碌脦鹿脧聛脦驴.</string>
    <string name="wont_save_min_length">脦聭脧聛脧聡脦碌脦炉脦卤 脦录脦碌 脦禄脦鹿脦鲁脧聦脧聞脦碌脧聛脦驴脧聟脧聜 脦卤脧聙脧聦 %d 脧聡脦卤脧聛脦卤脦潞脧聞脦庐脧聛脦碌脧聜, 脦麓脦碌脦陆 脦卤脧聙脦驴脦赂脦路脦潞脦碌脧聧脦驴脦陆脧聞脦卤脦鹿 脦卤脧聟脧聞脧聦脦录脦卤脧聞脦卤 脦鲁脦鹿脦卤 脦陆脦卤 脦卤脧聙脦驴脧聠脦碌脧聟脧聡脦赂脦碌脦炉 脦路 脦卤脧聙脧聨脦禄脦碌脦鹿脦卤 脦麓脦碌脦麓脦驴脦录脦颅脦陆脧聣脦陆.</string>
    <string name="advanced_filtering_help"><![CDATA[<small><a href="https://github.com/mattg101/portal/discussions">脦聽脧聛脦驴脧聡脧聣脧聛脦路脦录脦颅脦陆脦路 脧聝脧聧脦陆脧聞脦卤脦戮脦路 脧聠脦炉脦禄脧聞脧聛脧聣脦陆</a></small>]]></string>
    <string name="filter">脦娄脦炉脦禄脧聞脧聛脦驴</string>
</resources>
